<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Products>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Pro | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Pro Retail License Key (1 PC) – Instant Digital Delivery Upgrade your PC with a genuine Windows 10 Pro Retail license and unlock powerful features designed for work, study, gaming, and everyday use. Enjoy enhanced security, smooth performance, and a reliable Windows experience with a lifetime activation for one PC. With SAIVERA , your license is delivered digitally, so you can activate your system and get started within minutes. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Pro Retail license key Valid for activation on 1 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery Customer support if you need assistance Why Choose Windows 10 Pro? Whether you're upgrading an existing PC or installing Windows on a new one, the Pro edition offers advanced features beyond the Home version, making it ideal for professionals, students, businesses, and power users. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Lifetime activation for one PC Reactivate Windows after reinstalling on the same device Advanced security with BitLocker Remote Desktop support Hyper-V virtualization Fast, stable, and secure performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 10 Pro Activation: Online Devices: 1 PC Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same PC Transfer to another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, and your purchased license can be accessed anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Genuine and authentic license Friendly customer support whenever you need help Please note: Make sure you purchase the correct Windows edition for your device before completing your order. If you're unsure which version you need, our support team will be happy to assist you before your purchase.</Description>
    <Price>3.30</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10PRO</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-pro-retail-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091255_0000.png?v=1784409264</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Pro | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Pro Retail License Key (5 PC) – Instant Digital Delivery Upgrade your PC with a genuine Windows 10 Pro Retail license and unlock powerful features designed for work, study, gaming, and everyday use. Enjoy enhanced security, smooth performance, and a reliable Windows experience with a lifetime activation for one PC. With SAIVERA , your license is delivered digitally, so you can activate your system and get started within minutes. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Pro Retail license key Valid for activation on 5 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery Customer support if you need assistance Why Choose Windows 10 Pro? Whether you're upgrading an existing PC or installing Windows on a new one, the Pro edition offers advanced features beyond the Home version, making it ideal for professionals, students, businesses, and power users. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Lifetime activation for one PC Reactivate Windows after reinstalling on the same device Advanced security with BitLocker Remote Desktop support Hyper-V virtualization Fast, stable, and secure performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 10 Pro Activation: Online Devices: 5 PC Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same PC Transfer to another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, and your purchased license can be accessed anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Genuine and authentic license Friendly customer support whenever you need help Please note: Make sure you purchase the correct Windows edition for your device before completing your order. If you're unsure which version you need, our support team will be happy to assist you before your purchase.</Description>
    <Price>36.95</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10PRO5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-pro-retail-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0002.png?v=1784409491</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Home | OEM | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Home OEM License Key (1 PC) – Instant Digital Delivery Upgrade your PC with a genuine Windows 10 Home OEM license and enjoy a smooth, secure, and reliable Windows experience. Perfect for everyday computing, home use, work, and study, this lifetime license provides genuine Microsoft activation for one device. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Windows quickly and start using your PC without delay. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Home OEM license key Valid for activation on 1 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Home? Windows Home delivers everything you need for everyday computing, including fast performance, built-in security, and compatibility with the latest applications. Whether you're browsing the web, studying, streaming, or working from home, Windows Home offers a smooth and familiar experience. Key Features Genuine Microsoft OEM license Lifetime activation for one PC Online activation Automatically reactivates after reinstalling Windows on the same device Fast, secure, and reliable performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates Ideal for home, study, and everyday use License Information License Type: OEM Supported Edition: Windows 10 Home Activation: Online Devices: 1 PC Validity: Lifetime activation Motherboard Binding: The license becomes permanently linked to the activated motherboard. Reinstallation: Supported on the same device with automatic reactivation. Transfer to Another PC: Not supported. OEM licenses cannot be moved to a different device after activation. Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, and your purchased license can be accessed anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, make sure you select the correct Windows edition for your PC. OEM licenses are designed for a single device and become permanently associated with the motherboard after activation.</Description>
    <Price>5.20</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10HOME</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-pro-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0006.png?v=1784411222</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Home | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Home Retail License Key (5 PCs) – Instant Digital Delivery Activate up to 5 PCs with a genuine Windows 10 Home Retail license. Designed for families, businesses, and users with multiple devices, this Retail license provides lifetime activation, online activation, and the flexibility to reinstall Windows on the same activated PCs whenever needed. With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, so you can activate your devices quickly and enjoy a genuine Windows experience without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Home Retail license key Valid for activation on up to 5 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Home? Windows Home is built for everyday computing, offering a fast, secure, and intuitive experience. Whether you're browsing, studying, streaming, working remotely, or managing multiple household computers, Windows Home delivers the reliability and performance you need. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Activate up to 5 PCs Lifetime activation Online activation Reinstall Windows and reactivate on the same activated devices Fast, secure, and reliable performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates Perfect for home users, families, and multiple-device setups License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 10 Home Activation: Online Devices: Up to 5 PCs Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs Transfer to Another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your devices within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, ensure you select the correct Windows edition for your devices. If you're unsure which version is right for you, our support team will be happy to help before you place your order.</Description>
    <Price>27.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10HOME5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-home-oem-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0008.png?v=1784412006</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Pro | OEM | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Pro OEM License Key (1 PC) – Instant Digital Delivery Upgrade your PC with a genuine Windows 10 Pro OEM license and unlock powerful features designed for professionals, businesses, and advanced users. Enjoy lifetime activation, enhanced security, and reliable performance with an authentic Microsoft OEM license for one device. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your Windows installation quickly and start working without delay. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Pro OEM license key Valid for activation on 1 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Pro? Windows Pro is built for users who need more than the standard Home edition. Enjoy advanced security, professional management tools, Remote Desktop, BitLocker encryption, and powerful productivity features for business, work, study, or gaming. Key Features Genuine Microsoft OEM license Lifetime activation for one PC Online activation Automatically reactivates after reinstalling Windows on the same device Advanced security with BitLocker encryption Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Fast, stable, and secure performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: OEM Supported Edition: Windows 10 Pro Activation: Online Devices: 1 PC Validity: Lifetime activation Motherboard Binding: The license becomes permanently linked to the activated motherboard. Reinstallation: Supported on the same device with automatic reactivation. Transfer to Another PC: Not supported. OEM licenses cannot be moved to another device after activation. Important: This OEM license cannot be used to upgrade Windows Home to Windows Pro. It is intended for clean installations or devices already running the Pro edition. Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, and your purchased license can be accessed anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, ensure you select the correct Windows edition for your device. OEM licenses are designed for a single PC and become permanently associated with the motherboard after activation.</Description>
    <Price>5.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10PROOEM</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-home-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091255_0000_f53aad21-b63c-4b11-a658-c435ffc3f6ba.png?v=1784412912</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Pro | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Pro License Key (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Activate Windows 10 Pro on one PC using the official Microsoft Phone Activation method. This is a genuine activation solution for users who need a reliable Windows Pro license with fast digital delivery and easy activation instructions. With SAIVERA , your activation key and phone activation guide are delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your Windows installation quickly and securely. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Pro activation key Valid for activation on 1 PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Official Microsoft download link Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Pro? Windows Pro offers powerful features for professionals, students, businesses, and advanced users. Enjoy enhanced security, improved productivity, Remote Desktop, BitLocker encryption, and compatibility with the latest Windows updates. Key Features Genuine Microsoft activation key Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate 1 PC Advanced security with BitLocker Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Fast, stable, and secure performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Supported Edition: Windows 10 Pro Devices: 1 PC Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method. It is intended for a single activation on one PC. Reactivation after formatting, hardware changes, or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>3.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10PROPH</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-pro-oem-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091255_0000_e7cf73a7-e7d2-484f-b272-02e3ed2ad59b.png?v=1784413212</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Home | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Home License Key (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Activate Windows 10 Home on one PC using the official Microsoft Phone Activation method. This genuine activation solution is perfect for home users looking for a secure, reliable Windows license with fast digital delivery and simple activation. With SAIVERA , your activation key and phone activation instructions are delivered digitally within minutes, so you can activate Windows quickly and start using your PC without delay. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Home activation key Valid for activation on 1 PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Official Microsoft download link Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Home? Windows Home delivers everything you need for everyday computing, including a modern interface, reliable security, and smooth performance. It's the ideal choice for browsing, streaming, studying, working from home, and enjoying your favorite apps. Key Features Genuine Microsoft activation key Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate 1 PC Fast, stable, and secure Windows experience Compatible with the latest Windows updates Perfect for home, study, and everyday use License Information Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Supported Edition: Windows 10 Home Devices: 1 PC Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method. It is intended for a single activation on one PC. Reactivation after formatting, hardware changes, or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>3.49</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10HOMEPH</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-pro-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0006_66d5ea79-783a-45f9-918e-7ed5c306870c.png?v=1784415093</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Pro | Retail | 50 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Pro Retail License Key (50 PCs) – Instant Digital Delivery Activate up to 50 PCs with a genuine Windows 10 Pro Retail license. Ideal for businesses, IT professionals, schools, and organizations managing multiple devices, this Retail license provides lifetime activation, online activation, and the flexibility to reinstall Windows on the same activated PCs whenever needed. With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate multiple devices quickly and efficiently without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Pro Retail license key Valid for activation on up to 50 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Pro? Windows Pro is built for professionals and organizations that require advanced security, productivity, and management features. From BitLocker encryption and Remote Desktop to Hyper-V virtualization, Windows Pro provides everything needed for modern business and professional environments. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Activate up to 50 PCs Lifetime activation Online activation Reinstall Windows and reactivate on the same activated devices Advanced security with BitLocker encryption Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 10 Pro Activation: Online Devices: Up to 50 PCs Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs Transfer to Another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and begin activating your devices within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 30-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, ensure you select the correct Windows edition for your devices. If you need assistance choosing the right license, our support team will be happy to help before your purchase.</Description>
    <Price>44.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10PRO50</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-home-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0004.png?v=1784411675</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Pro | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Pro Volume License Key (20 PCs) – Instant Digital Delivery Activate up to 20 PCs with a genuine Windows 10 Pro Volume License . Designed for businesses, offices, schools, and IT professionals, this volume license offers a convenient way to activate multiple devices while enjoying the advanced features of Windows Pro. With SAIVERA , your volume license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to deploy Windows quickly across your devices without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Pro Volume license key Valid for activation on up to 20 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Pro? Windows Pro provides advanced tools for productivity, security, and device management, making it the ideal choice for organizations and professionals. Enjoy features such as BitLocker encryption, Remote Desktop, Hyper-V virtualization, and compatibility with the latest Windows updates. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Volume license Activate up to 20 PCs Lifetime activation Ideal for businesses, offices, and educational institutions Advanced security with BitLocker encryption Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Fast, stable, and secure Windows performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Volume License Supported Edition: Windows 10 Pro Devices: Up to 20 PCs Validity: Lifetime activation Activation: As provided with the supplied volume license key Instant Digital Delivery Your volume license key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and begin activating your devices within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, verify that you are selecting the correct Windows edition and license type for your environment. If you need assistance, our support team will be happy to help before your purchase.</Description>
    <Price>39.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10PRO20</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-pro-retail-50-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091257_0020.png?v=1784415338</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Enterprise LTSB 2015 | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>7.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-1011</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-pro-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_230537_0011.png?v=1783326151</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Enterprise LTSB 2016 | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>8.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-1011</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-enterprise-ltsb-2015-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_230537_0010.png?v=1783326126</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Enterprise LTSC 2019 | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>11.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-1011</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-enterprise-ltsb-2016-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_230537_0009.png?v=1783326101</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Enterprise LTSC 2021 | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>14.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-1011</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-enterprise-ltsc-2019-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_230536_0008.png?v=1783326077</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Enterprise | MAK Volume | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume License Key (1 PC) – Lifetime Activation Activate Windows 10 Enterprise on one PC with a genuine MAK Volume license. Designed for businesses, organizations, IT professionals, and advanced users, Windows 10 Enterprise provides powerful security, management, and productivity features for professional environments. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your Windows installation quickly and efficiently without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume license key Valid for activation on 1 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Enterprise? Windows 10 Enterprise is designed for organizations and professional users who require advanced security, device management, and enterprise-level features. It provides enhanced protection and control for demanding professional environments. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Volume license MAK (Multiple Activation Key) activation Activate 1 PC Lifetime license validity Advanced security and threat protection BitLocker drive encryption Windows Defender and enterprise security features Advanced device and application management Remote Desktop and virtualization support Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: MAK Volume Supported Edition: Windows 10 Enterprise Activation: Online Devices: 1 PC Validity: Lifetime license Reinstallation: Activation availability may depend on the remaining activations assigned to the MAK key Transfer to Another PC: Subject to Microsoft Volume Licensing activation terms Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your device efficiently. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This is a Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume license intended for activation on 1 PC. Make sure your device is compatible with the Enterprise edition and that you select the correct license type before purchasing.</Description>
    <Price>5.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10EN</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-enterprise-ltsb-2015-kn-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091257_0018.png?v=1784415678</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Enterprise | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume License Key (20 PCs) – Lifetime Activation Activate up to 20 PCs with a genuine Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume license. Designed for businesses, organizations, schools, IT professionals, and advanced users, Windows 10 Enterprise provides powerful security, management, and productivity features for professional environments. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate and manage multiple Windows installations efficiently without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume license key Valid for activation on up to 20 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Enterprise? Windows 10 Enterprise is designed for organizations and professional users who require advanced security, device management, and enterprise-level features. It provides enhanced protection and control for demanding professional environments. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Volume license MAK (Multiple Activation Key) activation Activate up to 20 PCs Lifetime license validity Advanced security and threat protection BitLocker drive encryption Windows Defender and enterprise security features Advanced device and application management Remote Desktop and virtualization support Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: MAK Volume Supported Edition: Windows 10 Enterprise Activation: Online Devices: Up to 20 PCs Validity: Lifetime license Reinstallation: Activation availability may depend on the remaining activations assigned to the MAK key Transfer to Another PC: Subject to Microsoft Volume Licensing activation terms Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your devices efficiently. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This is a Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume license intended for activation on up to 20 PCs. Make sure you select the correct license type for your organization before purchasing.</Description>
    <Price>16.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10EN20</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-enterprise-mak-volume-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091257_0016.png?v=1784415857</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Enterprise | MAK Volume | 50 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume License Key (50 PCs) – Lifetime Activation Activate up to 50 PCs with a genuine Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume license. Designed for businesses, organizations, IT professionals, and professional environments, Windows 10 Enterprise provides advanced security, management, and productivity features for multiple devices. With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally, allowing you to activate your devices quickly and efficiently without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume license key Valid for activation on up to 50 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Enterprise? Windows 10 Enterprise is designed for organizations that require advanced security, centralized management, and enhanced control over their IT environments. It is ideal for businesses and professional users managing multiple PCs and requiring enterprise-level Windows features. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Volume license MAK (Multiple Activation Key) activation Activate up to 50 PCs Lifetime license validity Advanced security and threat protection BitLocker drive encryption Windows Defender and enterprise security features Advanced device and application management Remote Desktop and virtualization support Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: MAK Volume Supported Edition: Windows 10 Enterprise Activation: Online Devices: Up to 50 PCs Validity: Lifetime license Reinstallation: Activation availability may depend on the remaining activations assigned to the MAK key Transfer to Another PC: Subject to Microsoft Volume Licensing activation terms Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your devices efficiently. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This is a Windows 10 Enterprise MAK Volume license intended for activation on up to 50 PCs. Make sure your devices are compatible with the Enterprise edition and that you select the correct license type before purchasing.</Description>
    <Price>19.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10EN50</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-enterprise-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0014.png?v=1784412588</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Education | Retail | 2 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>5.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10ED</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-enterprise-kn-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_230536_0004.png?v=1783325922</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Education | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>7.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10ED5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-education-retail-2-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_230536_0003.png?v=1783325886</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Education | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>9.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10ED20</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-education-n-retail-2-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_230536_0002.png?v=1783325855</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 IoT Enterprise LTSC 2021 | OEM NONSLP | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>16.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-1011loTEN21</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-pro-n-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_230536_0001.png?v=1783325817</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 10 Pro for Workstation | Retail | 2 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 10 Pro for Workstations Retail License Key (2 PCs) – Lifetime Activation Activate up to 2 PCs with a genuine Windows 10 Pro for Workstations Retail license. Designed for professionals, creators, engineers, developers, and power users, Windows Pro for Workstations delivers advanced performance, security, and reliability for demanding workloads. With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your devices quickly and enjoy a genuine Windows experience without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 10 Pro for Workstations Retail license key Valid for activation on up to 2 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 10 Pro for Workstations? Windows Pro for Workstations is designed for users who need more than standard Windows editions can offer. It provides advanced capabilities for demanding professional applications, intensive data processing, high-performance computing, and other resource-intensive workloads. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Activate up to 2 PCs Lifetime activation Online activation Reinstall Windows and reactivate on the same activated devices Support for high-performance hardware configurations Advanced security with BitLocker encryption Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Fast, stable, and reliable performance for demanding workloads Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 10 Pro for Workstations Activation: Online Devices: Up to 2 PCs Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs Transfer to Another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your devices within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, ensure you select the correct Windows edition for your devices. Windows Pro for Workstations is designed for high-performance professional use. If you're unsure whether this edition is right for your PC, our support team will be happy to help before you place your order.</Description>
    <Price>14.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-10PROWORK</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-11-lot-enterprise-oem-nonslp-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0012.png?v=1784412255</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2021 Home &amp; Business | Bind | 1 Mac | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2021 Home &amp; Business for Mac (1 Device) – Lifetime License – Instant Digital Delivery Get the essential Microsoft Office apps for your Mac with a genuine Office 2021 Home &amp; Business license. Designed for professionals, students, freelancers, and home users, this one-time purchase gives you lifetime access to powerful productivity tools with no monthly subscription required. With SAIVERA , your product key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to redeem your license through your Microsoft account and start using Office right away. What's Included Genuine Microsoft Office 2021 Home &amp; Business license key Valid for activation on 1 Mac Lifetime license (one-time purchase) Official Microsoft redemption instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2021 Home &amp; Business? Office 2021 Home &amp; Business includes the essential Microsoft applications you need to create documents, manage spreadsheets, deliver presentations, and handle email efficiently. It's the perfect solution for work, school, home offices, and everyday productivity without recurring subscription fees. Key Features One-time purchase with lifetime activation Licensed for 1 Mac Linked to your Microsoft account after activation No subscription or recurring payments Fast, secure, and easy activation Compatible with supported macOS versions Access to classic Office applications designed for productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2021 Home &amp; Business License Type: Retail Supported Device: 1 Mac Activation: Redeem through your Microsoft account Validity: Lifetime license Microsoft Account: Required for activation. The license becomes permanently linked to your Microsoft account. Redemption: https://setup.office.com Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2021 license key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office in just a few minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Make sure you're purchasing the correct Office edition for your device before placing your order. This license is valid for 1 Mac only and becomes permanently associated with your Microsoft account after activation.</Description>
    <Price>41.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;BU21MAC</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2021-home-business-bind-1-mac-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/18_20260621_133302_0017.png?v=1783285395</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2021 Professional Plus | Bind | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus (1 PC) – Lifetime License – Instant Digital Delivery Boost your productivity with a genuine Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus license for Windows. Whether you're working, studying, managing a business, or creating professional documents, Office 2021 Pro Plus includes all the essential Microsoft applications you need—without a monthly subscription. With SAIVERA , your product key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to redeem your license through your Microsoft account and start using Office right away. What's Included Genuine Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus license key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Lifetime license (one-time purchase) Official Microsoft redemption instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2021 Professional Plus? Office 2021 Professional Plus is the most complete Office suite for Windows, offering everything you need for business, education, and everyday productivity. Create professional documents, analyze data, manage emails, design publications, and deliver impressive presentations with Microsoft's trusted applications. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft OneNote Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher And other Office components included with Office Professional Plus 2021 Key Features One-time purchase with lifetime activation Licensed for 1 Windows PC Linked to your Microsoft account after activation No subscription or recurring payments Latest classic Office 2021 applications Fast, secure, and easy activation Ideal for professionals, businesses, students, and home users License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus License Type: Retail Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Redeem through your Microsoft account Validity: Lifetime license Microsoft Account: Required for activation. The license becomes permanently linked to your Microsoft account. Redemption: https://setup.office.com Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2021 Professional Plus license key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office in just a few minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 Windows PC only and is not compatible with Mac . Please ensure you are purchasing the correct Office edition before placing your order.</Description>
    <Price>64.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO21PC</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2021-home-business-bind-1-mac-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/16_20260621_133302_0015_822e696d-7b34-464c-9f15-4e8cc6a52fdb.png?v=1783285599</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2021 Professional Plus | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus (5 PCs) – Lifetime License – Instant Digital Delivery Equip up to 5 Windows PCs with a genuine Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus license. Perfect for families, businesses, offices, and users with multiple computers, this lifetime license provides access to Microsoft's complete productivity suite with no recurring subscription fees. With SAIVERA , your product key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Office quickly and start working without delay. What's Included Genuine Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus license key Valid for activation on up to 5 Windows PCs Lifetime license (one-time purchase) Easy activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2021 Professional Plus? Office 2021 Professional Plus includes Microsoft's most popular productivity applications, making it the ideal choice for business, education, remote work, and everyday office tasks. Create documents, analyze data, manage emails, build presentations, and more with one complete software package. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft OneNote Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Additional Office Professional Plus applications Key Features Activate up to 5 Windows PCs Lifetime activation No subscription or recurring payments Direct activation within your Office installation Reinstallation supported on the same activated PCs Complete Office 2021 Professional Plus suite Ideal for professionals, businesses, and multi-device users License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus License Type: Retail Supported Devices: Up to 5 Windows PCs Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Directly through your Office installation Microsoft Account: Not supported. This license cannot be linked to a Microsoft account. Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2021 Professional Plus license key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office in just a few minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for Windows PCs only and cannot be activated on macOS. It activates directly within your Office installation and cannot be linked to a Microsoft account . Please ensure you're purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>39.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO21PC5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2021-professional-plus-bind-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/17_20260621_133302_0016.png?v=1783285481</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2021 Professional Plus | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Get the complete Microsoft Office experience with a genuine Office 2021 Professional Plus license for Windows. Perfect for professionals, students, businesses, and home users, this edition includes all the essential Office applications you need to work, create, and stay productive. With SAIVERA , your activation key and Microsoft Phone Activation instructions are delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Office quickly and start using it right away. What's Included Genuine Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2021 Professional Plus? Office 2021 Professional Plus brings together Microsoft's most powerful productivity tools in one complete package. Whether you're creating documents, analyzing spreadsheets, managing emails, or building presentations, you'll have everything you need without paying monthly subscription fees. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft OneNote Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Additional Office Professional Plus applications Key Features Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate 1 Windows PC Complete Office 2021 Professional Plus suite No subscription required Fast and secure activation process Ideal for business, education, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method and is intended for a one-time activation . Reactivation after formatting, reinstalling Windows, or significant hardware changes is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>3.30</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO21PhAPC</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2021-professional-plus-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/16_20260621_133302_0015_6aea9bc5-6d53-47b7-8ceb-2d18a7d3cd62.png?v=1783285623</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2024 Home &amp; Business | Bind | 1 PC/MAC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2024 Home &amp; Business (1 PC or Mac) – Lifetime License – Instant Digital Delivery Work smarter with a genuine Microsoft Office 2024 Home &amp; Business license. Designed for professionals, students, freelancers, and home users, this one-time purchase gives you lifetime access to Microsoft's trusted productivity apps with no monthly subscription. With SAIVERA , your product key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to redeem your license through your Microsoft account and start using Office right away. What's Included Genuine Microsoft Office 2024 Home &amp; Business license key Valid for activation on 1 PC or 1 Mac Lifetime license (one-time purchase) Official Microsoft redemption instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2024 Home &amp; Business? Office 2024 Home &amp; Business includes the essential Microsoft applications you need to create documents, manage spreadsheets, deliver presentations, and handle email with confidence. Whether you're working from home, running a business, or managing personal projects, Office 2024 helps you stay productive every day. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Key Features One-time purchase with lifetime activation Licensed for 1 PC or 1 Mac Linked to your Microsoft account after activation No subscription or recurring payments Latest classic Office 2024 applications Fast, secure, and easy activation Perfect for work, business, study, and home use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2024 Home &amp; Business License Type: Retail Supported Devices: 1 PC or 1 Mac Activation: Redeem through your Microsoft account Validity: Lifetime license Microsoft Account: Required for activation. The license becomes permanently linked to your Microsoft account. Redemption: https://setup.office.com Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2024 Home &amp; Business license key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office in just a few minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 PC or 1 Mac and can be activated on a single device only. A Microsoft account is required, and the license becomes permanently associated with that account after activation.</Description>
    <Price>149.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;BU24</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2021-professional-plus-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0009.png?v=1783325698</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2019 Home &amp; Business | Bind | 1 MAC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business for Mac (1 Device) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Boost your productivity on macOS with a genuine Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business license. Designed for professionals, freelancers, students, and home users, this one-time activation gives you lifetime access to Microsoft's trusted productivity tools without any recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your product key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to redeem your license through your Microsoft account and start using Office right away. What's Included Genuine Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business activation key Valid for activation on 1 Mac Lifetime activation Official Microsoft redemption instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2019 Home &amp; Business? Office 2019 Home &amp; Business gives you the essential Microsoft applications to create documents, analyze spreadsheets, deliver presentations, and manage emails with confidence. Whether you're running a business, working remotely, or handling personal projects, you'll have the tools you need every day. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Key Features Lifetime activation Licensed for 1 Mac No subscription or recurring payments Bound to your Microsoft account after activation Fast and secure digital activation Optimized for supported macOS versions Perfect for business, work, study, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business Supported Device: 1 Mac Compatibility: macOS only Activation: Redeem through your Microsoft account Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: Required. The license will be permanently bound to your Microsoft account after activation. Redemption: https://setup.office.com Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2019 Home &amp; Business activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office in just a few minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 Mac only . A Microsoft account is required to activate the product, and the license will be permanently bound to your Microsoft account after activation. Please ensure you're purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>35.90</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;BU19</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2024-home-business-bind-1-pc-mac-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0008.png?v=1783325675</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2019 Professional Plus | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus (5 PCs) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Equip up to 5 Windows PCs with Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus and enjoy the complete Office experience without monthly subscription fees. Ideal for businesses, professionals, families, and users with multiple computers, this edition includes Microsoft's most popular productivity applications to help you work faster and more efficiently. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Office directly on your PC and start working right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on up to 5 Windows PCs Lifetime activation Easy activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2019 Professional Plus? Office 2019 Professional Plus brings together Microsoft's complete productivity suite for business, education, and everyday use. Create professional documents, analyze data, manage emails, design publications, and deliver outstanding presentations using industry-leading Office applications. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Lifetime activation Activate up to 5 Windows PCs No subscription or recurring payments Direct activation within your Office installation Reactivation supported after reinstalling Office on the same activated PCs Cannot be bound to a Microsoft account Complete Office Professional Plus suite Optimized for business, education, and professional use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus Supported Devices: Up to 5 Windows PCs Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Directly through your Office installation Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: This license cannot be bound to a Microsoft account. Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs. Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2019 Professional Plus activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and cannot be activated on macOS. It activates directly within your Office installation, supports reactivation on the same activated PCs after reinstallation, and cannot be bound to a Microsoft account . Please ensure you are purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>21.90</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO19</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2024-home-business-bind-1-pc-mac-lifetime-copy-1</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0007.png?v=1783325645</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2019 Professional Plus | Bind | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus (1 PC) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Unlock the full Microsoft Office experience with Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus for Windows. Designed for professionals, businesses, students, and power users, this edition includes Microsoft's complete productivity suite to help you create documents, analyze data, manage emails, and deliver impressive presentations—all with a one-time activation and no recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to redeem your product through your Microsoft account and start using Office right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Lifetime activation Official Microsoft redemption instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2019 Professional Plus? Office 2019 Professional Plus combines Microsoft's most powerful productivity applications in one package. Whether you're working from home, managing a business, studying, or handling professional projects, you'll have all the tools you need to stay productive every day. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Lifetime activation Licensed for 1 Windows PC No subscription or recurring payments Bound to your Microsoft account after activation Fast and secure digital activation Complete Office Professional Plus suite Perfect for business, education, and professional use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Redeem through your Microsoft account Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: Required. The license will be permanently bound to your Microsoft account after activation. Redemption: https://setup.office.com Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2019 Professional Plus activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office in just a few minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with 1 Windows PC only and is not compatible with macOS . A Microsoft account is required for activation, and the license will be permanently bound to your Microsoft account after activation. Please ensure you are purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>48.90</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO19</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2019-professional-plus-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/20_20260621_133302_0019_13dfcd45-14c2-4fda-8b0f-940db8b10149.png?v=1783285314</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2019 Professional Plus | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Get the complete Microsoft Office experience with Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus for Windows. Ideal for professionals, students, businesses, and home users, this edition includes Microsoft's full productivity suite to help you create documents, manage spreadsheets, organize emails, and deliver professional presentations without a subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, along with simple Microsoft Phone Activation instructions so you can activate Office and start working right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2019 Professional Plus? Office 2019 Professional Plus includes Microsoft's most popular productivity applications in one complete package. Whether you're working, studying, running a business, or managing personal projects, you'll have all the tools you need to stay productive every day. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate on 1 Windows PC Complete Office Professional Plus suite No subscription or recurring payments Fast and secure activation process Perfect for business, education, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2019 Professional Plus Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method and is intended for a one-time activation . Reactivation after formatting, reinstalling Windows, or significant hardware changes is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>5.75</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO19PhA</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2019-professional-plus-bind-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/20_20260621_133302_0019.png?v=1783285289</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2019 Home &amp; Student | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Student (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Get the essential Microsoft Office applications with Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Student for Windows. Designed for students, families, home users, and everyday productivity, this edition provides the core Office tools you need for school, work, and personal projects—all without a recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, along with simple Microsoft Phone Activation instructions so you can activate Office and start using it right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Student activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2019 Home &amp; Student? Office 2019 Home &amp; Student includes the classic Microsoft Office applications trusted by millions of users. Whether you're writing assignments, creating presentations, or organizing data, you'll have reliable productivity tools for learning, home, and everyday use. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Key Features Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate on 1 Windows PC Essential Office applications for students and home users No subscription or recurring payments Fast and secure activation process Perfect for school, study, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Student Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method and is intended for a one-time activation . Reactivation after formatting, reinstalling Windows, or significant hardware changes is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>7.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;ST19PhA</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2019-professional-plus-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0006.png?v=1783325583</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2019 Home &amp; Business | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Boost your productivity with Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business for Windows. Perfect for professionals, remote workers, students, and home users, this edition provides the essential Microsoft Office applications you need for everyday work, business, and personal projects—all without a recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, along with easy Microsoft Phone Activation instructions so you can activate Office and start working right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2019 Home &amp; Business? Office 2019 Home &amp; Business includes the essential Microsoft applications trusted by millions of users worldwide. Create professional documents, analyze spreadsheets, build presentations, and manage emails with reliable tools designed for work, study, and everyday productivity. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Key Features Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate on 1 Windows PC Essential Office applications for business and home use No subscription or recurring payments Fast and secure activation process Perfect for work, education, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method and is intended for a one-time activation . Reactivation after formatting, reinstalling Windows, or significant hardware changes is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>8.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;BU19PhA</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2019-home-student-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0005_88d38a00-dd07-4cd6-84c4-fc22ac0fe3d3.png?v=1783325558</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2019 Home &amp; Business | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business (1 PC) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Get the essential Microsoft Office applications with Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business for Windows. Perfect for professionals, small businesses, students, and home users, this edition delivers the tools you need to create documents, manage spreadsheets, prepare presentations, and handle emails without paying monthly subscription fees. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Office directly through your installation and start working right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Lifetime activation Easy activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2019 Home &amp; Business? Office 2019 Home &amp; Business includes Microsoft's essential productivity applications for everyday work and business tasks. Whether you're writing documents, organizing spreadsheets, creating presentations, or managing emails, you'll enjoy reliable performance with a one-time activation and no recurring subscription. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Key Features Lifetime activation Licensed for 1 Windows PC No subscription or recurring payments Direct activation within your Office installation Reactivation supported after reinstalling Office on the same PC Cannot be bound to a Microsoft account Perfect for business, home, and educational use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2019 Home &amp; Business Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Directly through your Office installation Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: This license cannot be bound to a Microsoft account. Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PC. Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2019 Home &amp; Business activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and cannot be activated on macOS. It activates directly through your Office installation, supports reactivation on the same PC after reinstallation, and cannot be bound to a Microsoft account . Please ensure you are purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>49.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;BU19PC</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2019-home-business-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0005.png?v=1783325530</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2016 Home &amp; Business | Bind | 1 MAC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Business for Mac (1 Device) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Boost your productivity on macOS with Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Business . Designed for professionals, freelancers, students, and home users, this edition provides the essential Microsoft Office applications you need for work, business, and everyday tasks—all with a one-time activation and no recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to redeem your product through your Microsoft account and start using Office right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Business activation key Valid for activation on 1 Mac Lifetime activation Official Microsoft redemption instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2016 Home &amp; Business? Office 2016 Home &amp; Business includes the essential Microsoft Office applications for creating documents, managing spreadsheets, building presentations, and handling email. It's an excellent choice for professionals, small businesses, remote workers, and home users who need reliable productivity software. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Key Features Lifetime activation Licensed for 1 Mac No subscription or recurring payments Bound to your Microsoft account after activation Fast and secure digital activation Optimized for supported macOS versions Ideal for business, work, study, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Business Supported Device: 1 Mac Compatibility: macOS only Activation: Redeem through your Microsoft account Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: Required. The license will be permanently bound to your Microsoft account after activation. Redemption: https://setup.office.com Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2016 Home &amp; Business activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office in just a few minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 Mac only . A Microsoft account is required to activate the product, and the license will be permanently bound to your Microsoft account after activation. Please ensure you're purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>24.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;BU16MAC</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2019-home-business-retail-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0004.png?v=1783325494</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2016 Professional Plus | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus (5 PCs) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Equip up to 5 Windows PCs with Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus and enjoy the complete Office experience without monthly subscription fees. Perfect for businesses, professionals, families, and users with multiple computers, this edition includes Microsoft's full productivity suite to help you work more efficiently every day. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Office directly through your installation and start working immediately. What's Included Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on up to 5 Windows PCs Lifetime activation Easy activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2016 Professional Plus? Office 2016 Professional Plus combines Microsoft's most powerful productivity applications in one complete suite. Create professional documents, analyze spreadsheets, manage emails, design publications, build databases, and deliver impressive presentations with software trusted by businesses worldwide. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Lifetime activation Activate up to 5 Windows PCs No subscription or recurring payments Direct activation within your Office installation Reactivation supported after reinstalling Office on the same activated PCs Cannot be bound to a Microsoft account Complete Office Professional Plus suite Perfect for business, education, and professional use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus Supported Devices: Up to 5 Windows PCs Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Directly through your Office installation Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: This license cannot be bound to a Microsoft account. Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs. Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2016 Professional Plus activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and cannot be activated on macOS. It activates directly through your Office installation, supports reactivation on the same activated PCs after reinstallation, and cannot be bound to a Microsoft account . Please ensure you are purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>24.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO16PC</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2016-home-business-bind-1-mac-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0003.png?v=1783325468</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2016 Professional Plus | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Unlock the complete Microsoft Office experience with Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus for Windows. Perfect for professionals, students, businesses, and home users, this edition includes Microsoft's full productivity suite to help you create documents, manage spreadsheets, organize emails, build databases, and deliver professional presentations without a subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, along with easy Microsoft Phone Activation instructions so you can activate Office and start working right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2016 Professional Plus? Office 2016 Professional Plus brings together Microsoft's complete productivity suite in one package. Whether you're working from home, managing a business, studying, or handling professional projects, you'll have all the tools you need to stay productive every day. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate on 1 Windows PC Complete Office Professional Plus suite No subscription or recurring payments Fast and secure activation process Perfect for business, education, and professional use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method and is intended for a one-time activation . Reactivation after formatting, reinstalling Windows, or significant hardware changes is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>5.75</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO16PCPhA</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2016-professional-plus-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/21_20260621_133302_0020_1c69dd47-7471-40d0-99e9-04b09c04955f.png?v=1783285186</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2016 Home &amp; Student | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Student (1 PC) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Get the essential Microsoft Office applications with Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Student for Windows. Designed for students, families, and home users, this edition provides the core Office tools you need for school, study, and everyday productivity without any recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to install and activate Office quickly using the official Microsoft installation files. What's Included Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Student activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Lifetime activation Official Microsoft installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2016 Home &amp; Student? Office 2016 Home &amp; Student includes Microsoft's essential productivity applications for everyday tasks. Whether you're preparing assignments, creating presentations, organizing data, or managing personal projects, you'll enjoy reliable performance with a one-time activation. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft OneNote Key Features Lifetime activation Licensed for 1 Windows PC No subscription or recurring payments Uses the official Microsoft Office installation files Cannot be bound to a Microsoft account Does not activate through setup.office.com Perfect for students, home users, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Student Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Direct activation using the installed Office software Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: This license cannot be bound to a Microsoft account. Installation: Requires the official Microsoft Office 2016 ISO installation files. This product cannot be redeemed through setup.office.com . Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2016 Home &amp; Student activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It cannot be bound to a Microsoft account and cannot be redeemed through setup.office.com . Installation requires the official Microsoft Office 2016 ISO files. Please ensure you are purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>8.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;ST16PC</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2016-professional-plus-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0001_657a5cad-e61b-4449-a1cd-c7ef0bedfbd0.png?v=1783325379</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2016 Home &amp; Business | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Business (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Get the essential Microsoft Office applications with Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Business for Windows. Designed for professionals, small businesses, students, and home users, this edition provides the tools you need to create documents, manage spreadsheets, prepare presentations, and handle emails without a recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, along with simple Microsoft Phone Activation instructions so you can activate Office and start working right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Business activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2016 Home &amp; Business? Office 2016 Home &amp; Business includes the essential Microsoft Office applications trusted by millions of users worldwide. Whether you're managing business tasks, working from home, or handling personal projects, you'll have reliable tools to stay productive every day. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Key Features Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate on 1 Windows PC Essential Office applications for business and home use No subscription or recurring payments Fast and secure activation process Perfect for work, education, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Business Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method and is intended for a one-time activation . Reactivation after formatting, reinstalling Windows, or significant hardware changes is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>8.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;BU16PhA</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2016-home-student-retail-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0002.png?v=1783325356</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2016 Home &amp; Student | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Student (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Get the essential Microsoft Office applications with Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Student for Windows. Designed for students, families, and home users, this edition provides the core Office tools you need for school, study, and everyday productivity without any recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, along with easy Microsoft Phone Activation instructions so you can activate Office and start using it right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Student activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2016 Home &amp; Student? Office 2016 Home &amp; Student includes the classic Microsoft Office applications trusted by millions of users worldwide. Whether you're preparing assignments, creating presentations, or organizing information, you'll have reliable productivity tools for learning and everyday use. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft OneNote Key Features Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate on 1 Windows PC Essential Office applications for students and home users No subscription or recurring payments Fast and secure activation process Perfect for school, study, and everyday productivity License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2016 Home &amp; Student Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method and is intended for a one-time activation . Reactivation after formatting, reinstalling Windows, or significant hardware changes is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>6.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-HO&amp;ST16PhA</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2016-home-business-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260705_224412_0001.png?v=1783325333</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2016 Professional Plus | Bind | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus (1 PC) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Unlock the full Microsoft Office experience with Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus for Windows. Designed for professionals, businesses, students, and power users, this edition includes Microsoft's complete productivity suite to help you create documents, analyze data, manage emails, build databases, and deliver professional presentations—all without a recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to redeem your product through your Microsoft account and start using Office right away. What's Included Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Lifetime activation Official Microsoft redemption instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2016 Professional Plus? Office 2016 Professional Plus combines Microsoft's complete productivity suite into one powerful package. Whether you're working from home, running a business, studying, or managing professional projects, you'll have everything you need to stay productive and organized. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Lifetime activation Licensed for 1 Windows PC No subscription or recurring payments Bound to your Microsoft account after activation Fast and secure digital activation Complete Office Professional Plus suite Perfect for business, education, and professional use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2016 Professional Plus Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Redeem through your Microsoft account Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: Required. The license will be permanently bound to your Microsoft account after activation. Redemption: https://setup.office.com Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2016 Professional Plus activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office in just a few minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . A Microsoft account is required for activation, and the license will be permanently bound to your Microsoft account after activation. Please ensure you are purchasing the correct version before completing your order.</Description>
    <Price>24.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO16</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2016-home-student-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/21_20260621_133302_0020.png?v=1783285157</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2013 Professional Plus | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2013 Professional Plus (5 PCs) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Equip up to 5 Windows PCs with Microsoft Office 2013 Professional Plus and enjoy the complete Office experience with a one-time purchase. Perfect for businesses, professionals, students, and users with multiple computers, this edition includes Microsoft's full productivity suite without any recurring subscription fees. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Office directly through your installation and start working immediately. What's Included Microsoft Office 2013 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on up to 5 Windows PCs Lifetime activation Easy activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2013 Professional Plus? Office 2013 Professional Plus provides Microsoft's complete productivity suite for work, education, and business. Create professional documents, analyze spreadsheets, build presentations, manage emails, create databases, and design publications using powerful applications trusted by millions of users worldwide. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Lifetime activation Activate up to 5 Windows PCs No subscription or recurring payments Direct activation within your Office installation Reactivation supported after reinstalling Office on the same activated PCs Cannot be bound to a Microsoft account Complete Office Professional Plus suite Ideal for business, education, and professional use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2013 Professional Plus Supported Devices: Up to 5 Windows PCs Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Directly through your Office installation Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: This license cannot be bound to a Microsoft account. Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs. Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2013 Professional Plus activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and cannot be activated on macOS. It activates directly through your Office installation, supports reactivation on the same activated PCs after reinstallation, and cannot be bound to a Microsoft account . Please ensure you purchase the correct Office edition and device count before completing your order, as delivered digital products cannot be exchanged for incorrect purchases.</Description>
    <Price>19.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO13PC5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2016-professional-plus-bind-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS_10_11_PRO_20260705_224411_0000.png?v=1783325310</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2013 Professional Plus | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2013 Professional Plus (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Unlock the complete Microsoft Office experience with Microsoft Office 2013 Professional Plus for Windows. Designed for professionals, businesses, students, and power users, this edition includes Microsoft's complete productivity suite to help you create documents, analyze data, manage emails, build databases, and deliver professional presentations without a recurring subscription. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, along with easy Microsoft Phone Activation instructions so you can activate Office and start working immediately. What's Included Microsoft Office 2013 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on 1 Windows PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2013 Professional Plus? Office 2013 Professional Plus includes Microsoft's complete collection of productivity applications for work, education, and business. Create professional documents, manage spreadsheets, build presentations, organize emails, create databases, and design publications with software trusted by millions of users worldwide. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate on 1 Windows PC Complete Office Professional Plus suite No subscription or recurring payments Fast and secure activation process Perfect for business, education, and professional use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2013 Professional Plus Supported Device: 1 Windows PC Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and Microsoft Phone Activation instructions will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and is not compatible with macOS . It uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method and is intended for a one-time activation . Reactivation after formatting, reinstalling Windows, or significant hardware changes is not guaranteed. Please ensure you purchase the correct Office edition before completing your order, as delivered digital products cannot be exchanged for incorrect purchases.</Description>
    <Price>5.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO13PhA</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2013-professional-plus-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/22_20260621_133302_0021.png?v=1783284780</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 2010 Professional Plus | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 2010 Professional Plus (5 PCs) – Lifetime Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Equip up to 5 Windows PCs with Microsoft Office 2010 Professional Plus and enjoy Microsoft's complete productivity suite with a one-time purchase. Ideal for businesses, professionals, students, and users managing multiple computers, this edition delivers powerful Office applications without any recurring subscription fees. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Office directly through your installation and start working immediately. What's Included Microsoft Office 2010 Professional Plus activation key Valid for activation on up to 5 Windows PCs Lifetime activation Easy activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 2010 Professional Plus? Office 2010 Professional Plus includes Microsoft's complete collection of productivity applications for work, education, and business. Create professional documents, manage spreadsheets, design presentations, organize emails, build databases, and publish professional content using reliable Office software trusted by millions of users. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft Access Microsoft Publisher Microsoft OneNote Key Features Lifetime activation Activate up to 5 Windows PCs No subscription or recurring payments Direct activation within your Office installation Reactivation supported after reinstalling Office on the same activated PCs Cannot be bound to a Microsoft account Complete Office Professional Plus suite Perfect for business, education, and professional use License Information Product: Microsoft Office 2010 Professional Plus Supported Devices: Up to 5 Windows PCs Compatibility: Windows only (Not compatible with macOS) Activation: Directly through your Office installation Validity: Lifetime activation Microsoft Account: This license cannot be bound to a Microsoft account. Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs. Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 2010 Professional Plus activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate Office within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day one-to-one replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is compatible with Windows PCs only and cannot be activated on macOS. It activates directly through your Office installation, supports reactivation on the same activated PCs after reinstallation, and cannot be bound to a Microsoft account . Please ensure you purchase the correct Office edition and device count before completing your order, as delivered digital products cannot be exchanged for incorrect purchases.</Description>
    <Price>17.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-PRO10</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2013-professional-plus-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260716_124638_0000_9c045dad-7693-4af8-bd86-c20de210ad4c.png?v=1784202478</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows Server 2022 Standard | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>4.99</Price>
    <Code>SERV-STN22</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-2010-professional-plus-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/9_20260621_133302_0008.png?v=1783284705</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows Server 2022 Datacenter | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>4.99</Price>
    <Code>SERV-DTC22</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-server-2022-standard-retail-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/10_20260621_133302_0009.png?v=1783284679</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows Server 2019 Standard | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>4.49</Price>
    <Code>SERV-STN19</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-server-2022-datacenter-retail-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/11_20260621_133302_0010.png?v=1783284652</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows Server 2019 Datacenter | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>4.99</Price>
    <Code>SERV-DTC19</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-server-2019-datacenter-retail-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/12_20260621_133302_0011.png?v=1783284620</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows Server 2019 Essentials | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>3.99</Price>
    <Code>SERV-ESS19</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-server-2019-essentials-retail-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/13_20260621_133302_0012.png?v=1783284586</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows Server 2016 Standard | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>4.99</Price>
    <Code>SERV-STN16</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-server-2016-standard-retail-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/14_20260621_133302_0013.png?v=1783284551</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows Server 2016 Datacenter | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description/>
    <Price>4.49</Price>
    <Code>SERV-DTC16</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-server-2016-datacenter-retail-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/15_20260621_133302_0014.png?v=1783284513</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>McAfee Total Protection | 1 Device | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>McAfee</Brand>
    <Description>McAfee Total Protection 2026 (1 Device, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with McAfee Total Protection 2026 , an all-in-one security solution designed to keep your PC, Mac, smartphone, or tablet safe from viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing attacks, and online threats. Enjoy advanced privacy tools, secure browsing, and reliable protection with a 1-year license for 1 device . With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your device right away. What's Included McAfee Total Protection 2026 license key Valid for 1 device 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose McAfee Total Protection? McAfee Total Protection offers complete security for your devices with powerful antivirus technology, secure VPN access, identity protection, password management, and privacy features. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, or working online, McAfee helps keep your personal information safe. Included Features Award-winning antivirus protection Secure VPN (Virtual Private Network) Identity and privacy protection Password Manager File Lock for sensitive files Real-time threat protection Key Features 1-year subscription Protects 1 device Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Real-time protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and phishing Safe browsing and online privacy tools Fast digital delivery License Information Product: McAfee Total Protection 2026 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 1 Device Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your license code Instant Digital Delivery Your McAfee license key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 device and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>4.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-Mc1D</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-server-2016-datacenter-retail-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/30_20260705_171258_0000.png?v=1783284391</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>McAfee Total Protection | 10 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>McAfee</Brand>
    <Description>McAfee Total Protection 2026 (1O Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with McAfee Total Protection 2026 , an all-in-one security solution designed to keep your PC, Mac, smartphone, or tablet safe from viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing attacks, and online threats. Enjoy advanced privacy tools, secure browsing, and reliable protection with a 1-year license for 10 devices . With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your device right away. What's Included McAfee Total Protection 2026 license key Valid for 10 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose McAfee Total Protection? McAfee Total Protection offers complete security for your devices with powerful antivirus technology, secure VPN access, identity protection, password management, and privacy features. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, or working online, McAfee helps keep your personal information safe. Included Features Award-winning antivirus protection Secure VPN (Virtual Private Network) Identity and privacy protection Password Manager File Lock for sensitive files Real-time threat protection Key Features 1-year subscription Protects 10 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Real-time protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and phishing Safe browsing and online privacy tools Fast digital delivery License Information Product: McAfee Total Protection 2026 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 10 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your license code Instant Digital Delivery Your McAfee license key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 10 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>12.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-Mc10D</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/mcafee-total-protection-10-device-1-year</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/31_20260705_171258_0001.png?v=1783284356</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>McAfee Total Protection | 1 Device | 3 Years</Name>
    <Brand>McAfee</Brand>
    <Description>McAfee Total Protection 2026 (1 Device, 3 Years) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with McAfee Total Protection 2026 , an all-in-one security solution designed to keep your PC, Mac, smartphone, or tablet safe from viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing attacks, and online threats. Enjoy advanced privacy tools, secure browsing, and reliable protection with a 3-years license for 1 device . With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your device right away. What's Included McAfee Total Protection 2026 license key Valid for 1 device 3-years subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose McAfee Total Protection? McAfee Total Protection offers complete security for your devices with powerful antivirus technology, secure VPN access, identity protection, password management, and privacy features. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, or working online, McAfee helps keep your personal information safe. Included Features Award-winning antivirus protection Secure VPN (Virtual Private Network) Identity and privacy protection Password Manager File Lock for sensitive files Real-time threat protection Key Features 3-years subscription Protects 1 device Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Real-time protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and phishing Safe browsing and online privacy tools Fast digital delivery License Information Product: McAfee Total Protection 2026 License Type: Subscription Validity: 3 Years Devices: 1 Device Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your license code Instant Digital Delivery Your McAfee license key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 device and includes a 3-years subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>17.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-Mc3Y</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/mcafee-total-protection-1-device-3-years</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/32_20260705_171258_0002.png?v=1783284331</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Norton 360 Deluxe | 3 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Norton</Brand>
    <Description>Norton 360 Deluxe (3 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Norton 360 Deluxe , a complete security solution designed to safeguard your devices against viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing, and other online threats. Enjoy advanced privacy features, secure browsing, and powerful real-time protection with a 1-year subscription for up to 3 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to secure your devices and start browsing with confidence right away. What's Included Norton 360 Deluxe activation key Valid for 3 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Norton 360 Deluxe? Norton 360 Deluxe combines award-winning security with powerful privacy tools to protect your personal information, online activities, and devices. Whether you're working, shopping, banking, gaming, or browsing the web, Norton helps keep you protected every day. Included Features Advanced antivirus protection Real-time protection against malware and ransomware Secure VPN for private browsing Online privacy protection Continuous security monitoring Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 3 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Secure browsing on public Wi-Fi with built-in VPN Designed for work, gaming, banking, shopping, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Norton 360 Deluxe License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 3 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Norton activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 3 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>15.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-NOR3D</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/mcafee-total-protection-1-device-3-years-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/33_20260705_171258_0003.png?v=1783284277</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Bitdefender Total Security 2026 | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Bitdefender</Brand>
    <Description>Bitdefender Total Security 2026 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect all your devices with Bitdefender Total Security 2026 , a comprehensive cybersecurity solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing, and other online threats. Enjoy powerful security, enhanced privacy, and reliable performance with a 1-year subscription for up to 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to secure your devices and get protected right away. What's Included Bitdefender Total Security 2026 activation key Valid for 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Bitdefender Total Security? Bitdefender Total Security combines advanced cybersecurity technologies with privacy and performance features to keep your devices safe while you work, browse, shop, bank, or play online. Its intelligent protection runs efficiently in the background without slowing down your devices. Included Features Advanced antivirus protection VPN with up to 200 MB of secure browsing per day Password Manager Data breach detection Real-time protection against online threats Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Real-time protection against malware, ransomware, and cyber threats Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Bitdefender Total Security 2026 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Bitdefender activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>28.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-BIT26</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/norton-360-deluxe-3-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/35_20260705_171258_0005.png?v=1783284243</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Bitdefender Internet Security 2025 | 3 PC | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Bitdefender</Brand>
    <Description>Bitdefender Internet Security 2025 (3 PCs, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Keep your Windows computers protected with Bitdefender Internet Security 2025 , an advanced security solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing, and other online threats. Enjoy reliable protection, enhanced privacy, and secure online banking with a 1-year subscription for up to 3 Windows PCs . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Bitdefender Internet Security 2025 activation key Valid for 3 Windows PCs 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Bitdefender Internet Security? Bitdefender Internet Security provides multi-layered protection to keep your devices safe from evolving cyber threats while maintaining excellent system performance. Whether you're shopping, banking, browsing, or working online, it helps protect your personal information and online activities. Included Features Advanced multi-layered protection against online threats Real-time antivirus protection Secure VPN with up to 200 MB of data per day Dedicated secure browser for online banking and payments Advanced web protection Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 3 Windows PCs Real-time protection against malware, ransomware, phishing, and cyber threats Designed for secure browsing, online banking, shopping, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Bitdefender Internet Security 2025 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 3 Windows PCs Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Bitdefender activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 3 Windows PCs and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>10.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-BIT25</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/bitdefender-total-security-2026-5-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/36_20260705_171258_0006.png?v=1783284208</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Breachguard | 1 PC | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>Avast BreachGuard (1 PC, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Take control of your online privacy with Avast BreachGuard , an advanced privacy protection service that continuously monitors the dark web for leaked personal information and compromised passwords. Stay informed about data breaches and protect your digital identity with a 1-year subscription for 1 PC . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your subscription and start protecting your personal information right away. What's Included Avast BreachGuard activation key Valid for 1 PC 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Avast BreachGuard? Avast BreachGuard helps you stay ahead of cybercriminals by monitoring the dark web for leaked personal information. If your passwords or personal data appear in a data breach, you'll receive notifications so you can take immediate action to secure your accounts. Included Features Dark web monitoring for leaked personal data Detection of weak or compromised passwords Real-time notifications for new data breaches Privacy and identity protection tools Key Features 1-year subscription Protect 1 PC Continuous monitoring of your personal information Early alerts for compromised accounts Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Avast BreachGuard License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 1 PC Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Avast BreachGuard activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your subscription within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 PC and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>2.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-AVBR1</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/bitdefender-total-security-2025-3-pc-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/38_20260705_171258_0008.png?v=1783283999</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Breachguard | 3 PC | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>Avast BreachGuard (3 PCs, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Take control of your online privacy with Avast BreachGuard , an advanced privacy protection service that continuously monitors the dark web for leaked personal information and compromised passwords. Stay informed about data breaches and protect your digital identity with a 1-year subscription for 3 PCs . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your subscription and start protecting your personal information right away. What's Included Avast BreachGuard activation key Valid for 3 PCs 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Avast BreachGuard? Avast BreachGuard helps you stay ahead of cybercriminals by monitoring the dark web for leaked personal information. If your passwords or personal data appear in a data breach, you'll receive notifications so you can take immediate action to secure your accounts. Included Features Dark web monitoring for leaked personal data Detection of weak or compromised passwords Real-time notifications for new data breaches Privacy and identity protection tools Key Features 1-year subscription Protect 3 PCs Continuous monitoring of your personal information Early alerts for compromised accounts Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Avast BreachGuard License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 3 PCs Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Avast BreachGuard activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your subscription within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 3 PCs and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>6.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-AVBR3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-breachguard-1-pc-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/39_20260705_171258_0009.png?v=1783283961</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Premium Security 2026 | 1 Device | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>AVAST Premium Security 2026 (1 Device, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your Windows PC with AVAST Premium Security 2026 , an advanced cybersecurity solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing attacks, and other online threats. Enjoy reliable real-time protection, enhanced privacy, and safe browsing with a 1-year subscription for 1 device . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your device right away. What's Included AVAST Premium Security 2026 activation key Valid for 1 Windows device 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose AVAST Premium Security? AVAST Premium Security provides powerful protection for your PC with advanced threat detection, ransomware defense, and online privacy features. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, gaming, or working online, AVAST helps keep your personal data and device secure without slowing down your system. Included Features Advanced antivirus protection Real-time protection against malware and ransomware Safe web browsing Online privacy protection Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect 1 Windows device Real-time protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and online threats Optimized performance with minimal system impact Designed for work, gaming, banking, shopping, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: AVAST Premium Security 2026 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 1 Windows Device Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your AVAST activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 Windows device and includes a 1-year subscription . The activation key should be activated within the specified validity period and is not compatible with existing subscriptions of the same type. Please verify compatibility before purchasing.</Description>
    <Price>5.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-AVPR26</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-breachguard-3-pc-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/41_20260705_171259_0011.png?v=1783283929</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Premium Security 2020 | 1 PC | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>AVAST Premium Security 2020 (1 PC, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your Windows PC with AVAST Premium Security 2020 , a comprehensive security solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing attacks, and other online threats. Enjoy reliable protection, secure browsing, and enhanced privacy with a 1-year subscription for 1 PC . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your device right away. What's Included AVAST Premium Security 2020 activation key Valid for 1 Windows PC 1-year subscription Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose AVAST Premium Security? AVAST Premium Security provides advanced protection for your PC against today's most common cyber threats. Whether you're browsing the web, shopping online, banking, or working remotely, AVAST helps keep your personal information and files safe with intelligent real-time security. Included Features Advanced antivirus protection Real-time protection against malware and ransomware Protection against phishing and fake websites Identity theft and data protection Security scanning for websites Customizable security settings Key Features 1-year subscription Protect 1 Windows PC Secure browsing, shopping, banking, and everyday use Real-time protection against online threats Optimized performance with minimal system impact Fast digital delivery License Information Product: AVAST Premium Security 2020 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 1 Windows PC Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your AVAST activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 Windows PC and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>6.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-AVPR20PC1</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-premium-security-2026-1-device-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/42_20260705_171259_0012.png?v=1783283898</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Premium Security 2020 | 3 PC | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>AVAST Premium Security 2020 (3 PCs, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your Windows PC with AVAST Premium Security 2020 , a comprehensive security solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing attacks, and other online threats. Enjoy reliable protection, secure browsing, and enhanced privacy with a 1-year subscription for 3 PCs . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your device right away. What's Included AVAST Premium Security 2020 activation key Valid for 3 PCs 1-year subscription Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose AVAST Premium Security? AVAST Premium Security provides advanced protection for your PC against today's most common cyber threats. Whether you're browsing the web, shopping online, banking, or working remotely, AVAST helps keep your personal information and files safe with intelligent real-time security. Included Features Advanced antivirus protection Real-time protection against malware and ransomware Protection against phishing and fake websites Identity theft and data protection Security scanning for websites Customizable security settings Key Features 1-year subscription Protect 3 PCs Secure browsing, shopping, banking, and everyday use Real-time protection against online threats Optimized performance with minimal system impact Fast digital delivery License Information Product: AVAST Premium Security 2020 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 3 PCs Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your AVAST activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 3 PCs and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>9.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-AVPR20PC3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-premium-security-2020-1-pc-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/43_20260705_171259_0013.png?v=1783283853</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Ultimate | 1 PC | 2 Years</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>AVAST Ultimate (1 PC, 2 Years) – Instant Digital Delivery Get the complete AVAST security experience with AVAST Ultimate , an all-in-one software suite that combines advanced antivirus protection, secure VPN, password management, and PC optimization. Enjoy maximum security, privacy, and performance with a 2-year subscription for 1 Windows PC . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate all included features and protect your PC immediately. What's Included AVAST Ultimate activation key Valid for 1 Windows PC 2-year subscription Activation and setup instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose AVAST Ultimate? AVAST Ultimate combines multiple premium security and performance tools into one powerful package. Protect your device from cyber threats, secure your online privacy, manage your passwords safely, and keep your PC running at its best with a single license. Included Applications AVAST Premium Security AVAST SecureLine VPN AVAST Cleanup Premium AVAST Passwords Premium Key Features 2-year subscription Protect 1 Windows PC Advanced antivirus and ransomware protection Secure VPN with bank-grade encryption Password management for secure logins PC cleanup and performance optimization Protection for your home Wi-Fi network Fast digital delivery License Information Product: AVAST Ultimate License Type: Subscription Validity: 2 Years Devices: 1 Windows PC Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your AVAST Ultimate activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate all included applications within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and setup assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 Windows PC and includes a 2-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>30.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-AVUL2Y</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-premium-security-2020-3-pc-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/44_20260705_171259_0014.png?v=1783283706</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Ultimate | 1 PC | 3 Years</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>AVAST Ultimate (1 PC, 3 Years) – Instant Digital Delivery Get the complete AVAST security experience with AVAST Ultimate , an all-in-one software suite that combines advanced antivirus protection, secure VPN, password management, and PC optimization. Enjoy maximum security, privacy, and performance with a 3-year subscription for 1PC . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate all included features and protect your PC immediately. What's Included AVAST Ultimate activation key Valid for 1 PC 3-year subscription Activation and setup instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose AVAST Ultimate? AVAST Ultimate combines multiple premium security and performance tools into one powerful package. Protect your device from cyber threats, secure your online privacy, manage your passwords safely, and keep your PC running at its best with a single license. Included Applications AVAST Premium Security AVAST SecureLine VPN AVAST Cleanup Premium AVAST Passwords Premium Key Features 3-year subscription Protect 1 PC Advanced antivirus and ransomware protection Secure VPN with bank-grade encryption Password management for secure logins PC cleanup and performance optimization Protection for your home Wi-Fi network Fast digital delivery License Information Product: AVAST Ultimate License Type: Subscription Validity: 3 Years Devices: 1 PC Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your AVAST Ultimate activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate all included applications within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and setup assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 PC and includes a 3-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>56.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-AVUL3Y</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-ultimate-1-pc-2-years-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/45_20260705_171259_0015.png?v=1783283676</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Ultimate | 1 PC | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>AVAST Ultimate (1 PC, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Get the complete AVAST security experience with AVAST Ultimate , an all-in-one software suite that combines advanced antivirus protection, secure VPN, password management, and PC optimization. Enjoy maximum security, privacy, and performance with a 1-year subscription for 1PC . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate all included features and protect your PC immediately. What's Included AVAST Ultimate activation key Valid for 1 PC 1-year subscription Activation and setup instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose AVAST Ultimate? AVAST Ultimate combines multiple premium security and performance tools into one powerful package. Protect your device from cyber threats, secure your online privacy, manage your passwords safely, and keep your PC running at its best with a single license. Included Applications AVAST Premium Security AVAST SecureLine VPN AVAST Cleanup Premium AVAST Passwords Premium Key Features 1-year subscription Protect 1 PC Advanced antivirus and ransomware protection Secure VPN with bank-grade encryption Password management for secure logins PC cleanup and performance optimization Protection for your home Wi-Fi network Fast digital delivery License Information Product: AVAST Ultimate License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 1 PC Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your AVAST Ultimate activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate all included applications within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and setup assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 PC and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>14.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-AVUL1Y</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-ultimate-1-pc-3-years-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/46_20260705_171259_0016.png?v=1783283646</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Total Security 2024 | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Total Security 2024 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Kaspersky Total Security 2024 , a premium cybersecurity solution that safeguards your devices against viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing, and other online threats. Enjoy advanced privacy features, secure online payments, and powerful protection with a 1-year subscription for up to 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Total Security 2024 activation key Valid for 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Kaspersky Total Security? Kaspersky Total Security delivers complete protection for your devices with advanced security technologies, privacy tools, and family safety features. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, working, or gaming, Kaspersky helps keep your personal information and devices secure. Included Features Advanced antivirus protection Real-time anti-ransomware protection Webcam protection Password Manager Secure VPN Advanced parental controls Data encryption Secure online payment protection with bank-grade encryption Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 devices Real-time protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and cyber threats Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Designed for work, gaming, banking, shopping, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Total Security 2024 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>50.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSP24</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-ultimate-1-pc-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/48_20260705_171259_0018.png?v=1783283617</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Total Security 2025 | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Total Security 2025 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Kaspersky Total Security 2025 , a premium cybersecurity solution that safeguards your devices against viruses, malware, ransomware, phishing, and other online threats. Enjoy advanced privacy features, secure online payments, and powerful protection with a 1-year subscription for up to 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Total Security 2025 activation key Valid for 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Kaspersky Total Security? Kaspersky Total Security delivers complete protection for your devices with advanced security technologies, privacy tools, and family safety features. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, working, or gaming, Kaspersky helps keep your personal information and devices secure. Included Features Advanced antivirus protection Real-time anti-ransomware protection Webcam protection Password Manager Secure VPN Advanced parental controls Data encryption Secure online payment protection with bank-grade encryption Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 devices Real-time protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and cyber threats Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Designed for work, gaming, banking, shopping, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Total Security 2025 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>48.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSP25</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-total-security-2024-5-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/49_20260705_171259_0019.png?v=1783283575</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Antivirus 2024 | 1 Device | 2 Years</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2024 (1 Device, 2 Years) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your Windows PC with Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2024 , a trusted security solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, spyware, cryptomining malware, and other online threats. Enjoy reliable real-time protection with a 2-year license for 1 device . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your PC right away. What's Included Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2024 activation key Valid for 1 Windows device 2-year license Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Kaspersky Anti-Virus? Kaspersky Anti-Virus provides essential protection against today's most common cyber threats while maintaining excellent system performance. It continuously monitors your device to help keep your files, personal information, and operating system safe. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Protection against ransomware Defense against spyware and malware Protection against cryptolockers Prevention of cryptomining malware infections Continuous security updates Key Features 2-year license Protect 1 Windows device Real-time protection against viruses and online threats Optimized performance with minimal system impact Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2024 License Type: Subscription Validity: 2 Years Devices: 1 Windows Device Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 Windows device and includes a 2-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>37.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPANT24</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-total-security-2025-5-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/52_20260705_171259_0022.png?v=1783283536</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Antivirus 2024 | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2024 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your Windows devices with Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2024 , a trusted security solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, spyware, cryptomining malware, and other online threats. Enjoy reliable real-time protection with a 1-year license for up to 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2024 activation key Valid for up to 5 Windows devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Kaspersky Anti-Virus? Kaspersky Anti-Virus provides essential protection against today's most common cyber threats while maintaining excellent system performance. It continuously monitors your devices to help keep your files, personal information, and operating systems safe. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Protection against ransomware Defense against spyware and malware Protection against cryptolockers Prevention of cryptomining malware infections Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 Windows devices Real-time protection against viruses and online threats Optimized performance with minimal system impact Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2024 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Windows Devices Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 Windows devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>39.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPANT24D5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-antivirus-2024-1-device-2-years-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/53_20260705_171259_0023.png?v=1783283493</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Antivirus 2025 | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2025 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your Windows devices with Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2025 , a trusted security solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, spyware, cryptomining malware, and other online threats. Enjoy reliable real-time protection with a 1-year license for up to 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2025 activation key Valid for up to 5 Windows devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Kaspersky Anti-Virus? Kaspersky Anti-Virus provides essential protection against today's most common cyber threats while maintaining excellent system performance. It continuously monitors your devices to help keep your files, personal information, and operating systems safe. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Protection against ransomware Defense against spyware and malware Protection against cryptolockers Prevention of cryptomining malware infections Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 Windows devices Real-time protection against viruses and online threats Optimized performance with minimal system impact Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2025 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Windows Devices Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 Windows devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>21.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPANT25D5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-antivirus-2024-5-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/55_20260705_171259_0025.png?v=1783283449</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Antivirus 2025 | 3 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2025 (3 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your Windows devices with Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2025 , a trusted security solution designed to defend against viruses, malware, ransomware, spyware, cryptomining malware, and other online threats. Enjoy reliable real-time protection with a 1-year license for up to 3 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2025 activation key Valid for up to 3 Windows devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Kaspersky Anti-Virus? Kaspersky Anti-Virus provides essential protection against today's most common cyber threats while maintaining excellent system performance. It continuously monitors your devices to help keep your files, personal information, and operating systems safe. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Protection against ransomware Defense against spyware and malware Protection against cryptolockers Prevention of cryptomining malware infections Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 3 Windows devices Real-time protection against viruses and online threats Optimized performance with minimal system impact Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Anti-Virus 2025 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 3 Windows Devices Supported Platform: Windows Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 3 Windows devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>20.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPANT25D3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-antivirus-2025-5-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/56_20260705_171259_0026.png?v=1783283354</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Premium 2023 | 3 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Premium 2023 (3 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Kaspersky Premium 2023 , an advanced all-in-one security solution that combines powerful antivirus protection, unlimited VPN, password management, and privacy tools. Enjoy premium cybersecurity with a 1-year subscription for up to 3 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Premium 2023 activation key Valid for up to 3 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email 24/7 technical support Why Choose Kaspersky Premium? Kaspersky Premium provides complete protection for your devices, identity, and privacy. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, working, or gaming, it helps keep your personal information safe with advanced security technologies and premium privacy features. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Unlimited secure VPN Password Manager Real-time data breach monitoring Documents Vault for sensitive files Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 3 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Advanced protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and online threats Designed for secure browsing, banking, shopping, gaming, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Premium 2023 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 3 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance 24/7 technical support Please note: This license is valid for up to 3 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>48.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPPR23D3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-antivirus-2025-3-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/58_20260705_171300_0028.png?v=1783283298</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Premium 2023 | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Premium 2023 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Kaspersky Premium 2023 , an advanced all-in-one security solution that combines powerful antivirus protection, unlimited VPN, password management, and privacy tools. Enjoy premium cybersecurity with a 1-year subscription for up to 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Premium 2023 activation key Valid for up to 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email 24/7 technical support Why Choose Kaspersky Premium? Kaspersky Premium provides complete protection for your devices, identity, and privacy. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, working, or gaming, it helps keep your personal information safe with advanced security technologies and premium privacy features. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Unlimited secure VPN Password Manager Real-time data breach monitoring Documents Vault for sensitive files Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Advanced protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and online threats Designed for secure browsing, banking, shopping, gaming, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Premium 2023 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance 24/7 technical support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>55.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPPR23D5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-antivirus-2023-3-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/59_20260705_171300_0029.png?v=1783283265</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Premium 2024 | 3 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Premium 2024 (3 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Kaspersky Premium 2024 , an advanced all-in-one security solution that combines powerful antivirus protection, unlimited VPN, password management, and privacy tools. Enjoy premium cybersecurity with a 1-year subscription for up to 3 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Premium 2024 activation key Valid for up to 3 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email 24/7 technical support Why Choose Kaspersky Premium? Kaspersky Premium provides complete protection for your devices, identity, and privacy. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, working, or gaming, it helps keep your personal information safe with advanced security technologies and premium privacy features. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Unlimited secure VPN Password Manager Real-time data breach monitoring Documents Vault for sensitive files Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 3 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Advanced protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and online threats Designed for secure browsing, banking, shopping, gaming, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Premium 2024 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 3 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance 24/7 technical support Please note: This license is valid for up to 3 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>42.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPPR24D3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-antivirus-2024-3-devices-1-year</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/60_20260705_171300_0030.png?v=1783283233</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Premium 2024 | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Premium 2024 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Kaspersky Premium 2024 , an advanced all-in-one security solution that combines powerful antivirus protection, unlimited VPN, password management, and privacy tools. Enjoy premium cybersecurity with a 1-year subscription for up to 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Premium 2024 activation key Valid for up to 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email 24/7 technical support Why Choose Kaspersky Premium? Kaspersky Premium provides complete protection for your devices, identity, and privacy. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, working, or gaming, it helps keep your personal information safe with advanced security technologies and premium privacy features. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Unlimited secure VPN Password Manager Real-time data breach monitoring Documents Vault for sensitive files Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Advanced protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and online threats Designed for secure browsing, banking, shopping, gaming, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Premium 2024 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance 24/7 technical support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>51.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPPR24D5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-premium-2024-3-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/61_20260705_171300_0031.png?v=1783283199</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Premium 2025 | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Premium 2025 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Kaspersky Premium 2025 , an advanced all-in-one security solution that combines powerful antivirus protection, unlimited VPN, password management, and privacy tools. Enjoy premium cybersecurity with a 1-year subscription for up to 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Premium 2025 activation key Valid for up to 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email 24/7 technical support Why Choose Kaspersky Premium? Kaspersky Premium provides complete protection for your devices, identity, and privacy. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, working, or gaming, it helps keep your personal information safe with advanced security technologies and premium privacy features. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Unlimited secure VPN Password Manager Real-time data breach monitoring Documents Vault for sensitive files Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Advanced protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and online threats Designed for secure browsing, banking, shopping, gaming, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Premium 2025 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance 24/7 technical support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>41.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPPR25D5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-premium-2024-5-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/65_20260705_171300_0035.png?v=1783283168</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky Premium 2025 | 3 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky Premium 2025 (3 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your digital life with Kaspersky Premium 2025 , an advanced all-in-one security solution that combines powerful antivirus protection, unlimited VPN, password management, and privacy tools. Enjoy premium cybersecurity with a 1-year subscription for up to 3 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your protection and secure your devices right away. What's Included Kaspersky Premium 2025 activation key Valid for up to 3 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email 24/7 technical support Why Choose Kaspersky Premium? Kaspersky Premium provides complete protection for your devices, identity, and privacy. Whether you're browsing, shopping, banking, working, or gaming, it helps keep your personal information safe with advanced security technologies and premium privacy features. Included Features Advanced real-time antivirus protection Unlimited secure VPN Password Manager Real-time data breach monitoring Documents Vault for sensitive files Continuous security updates Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 3 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Advanced protection against viruses, malware, ransomware, and online threats Designed for secure browsing, banking, shopping, gaming, and everyday use Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky Premium 2025 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 3 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your protection within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance 24/7 technical support Please note: This license is valid for up to 3 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>39.95</Price>
    <Code>ANTV-KSPPR25D3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-premium-2025-5-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Antivirus &amp; Security Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/64_20260705_171300_0034.png?v=1783283131</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Surfshark Starter VPN | Unlimited Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Surfshark</Brand>
    <Description>Surfshark Starter VPN (Unlimited Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Browse the internet securely and privately with Surfshark Starter VPN . Encrypt your internet connection, protect your personal data, and enjoy unrestricted online access across all your devices with a 1-year subscription for unlimited devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your VPN and start browsing securely right away. What's Included Surfshark Starter VPN activation key Valid for unlimited devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Technical customer support Why Choose Surfshark Starter VPN? Surfshark Starter VPN keeps your online activity private by creating an encrypted connection between your devices and the internet. Whether you're browsing on public Wi-Fi, streaming, shopping, or working remotely, Surfshark helps protect your privacy across all your devices. Included Features Secure encrypted VPN connection Unlimited device support Built-in Ad Blocker Cookie Pop-up Blocker Bypasser (Split Tunneling) Rotating IP Dynamic MultiHop Masked email generator Personal detail generator Key Features 1-year subscription Protect unlimited devices with one subscription Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, iOS, and other supported platforms Encrypted browsing and enhanced online privacy Ideal for streaming, remote work, gaming, and public Wi-Fi Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Surfshark Starter VPN License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Unlimited Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, iOS, Linux, Smart TVs, and supported browsers Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Surfshark activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your subscription within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional technical support Please note: This license is valid for unlimited devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>58.95</Price>
    <Code>VPN-SURF1</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-premium-2025-3-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Network Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/71_20260705_171300_0041.png?v=1783282928</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Surfshark Starter VPN | Unlimited Devices | 2 Years</Name>
    <Brand>Surfshark</Brand>
    <Description>Surfshark Starter VPN (Unlimited Devices, 2 Years) – Instant Digital Delivery Browse the internet securely and privately with Surfshark Starter VPN . Encrypt your internet connection, protect your personal data, and enjoy unrestricted online access across all your devices with a 2-year subscription for unlimited devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your VPN and start browsing securely right away. What's Included Surfshark Starter VPN activation key Valid for unlimited devices 2-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Technical customer support Why Choose Surfshark Starter VPN? Surfshark Starter VPN keeps your online activity private by creating an encrypted connection between your devices and the internet. Whether you're browsing on public Wi-Fi, streaming, shopping, or working remotely, Surfshark helps protect your privacy across all your devices. Included Features Secure encrypted VPN connection Unlimited device support Built-in Ad Blocker Cookie Pop-up Blocker Bypasser (Split Tunneling) Rotating IP Dynamic MultiHop Masked email generator Personal detail generator Key Features 2-year subscription Protect unlimited devices with one subscription Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, iOS, and other supported platforms Encrypted browsing and enhanced online privacy Ideal for streaming, remote work, gaming, and public Wi-Fi Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Surfshark Starter VPN License Type: Subscription Validity: 2 Years Devices: Unlimited Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, iOS, Linux, Smart TVs, and supported browsers Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Surfshark activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your subscription within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional technical support Please note: This license is valid for unlimited devices and includes a 2-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>92.95</Price>
    <Code>VPN-SURF2</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/surfshark-starter-vpn-unlimited-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Network Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/72_20260705_171300_0042.png?v=1783282907</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Surfshark Starter VPN | Unlimited Devices | 30 Days</Name>
    <Brand>Surfshark</Brand>
    <Description>Surfshark Starter VPN (Unlimited Devices, 30 Days) – Instant Digital Delivery Browse the internet securely and privately with Surfshark Starter VPN . Encrypt your internet connection, protect your personal data, and enjoy unrestricted online access across all your devices with a 30-day subscription for unlimited devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your VPN and start browsing securely right away. What's Included Surfshark Starter VPN activation key Valid for unlimited devices 30-day subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Technical customer support Why Choose Surfshark Starter VPN? Surfshark Starter VPN keeps your online activity private by creating an encrypted connection between your devices and the internet. Whether you're browsing on public Wi-Fi, streaming, shopping, or working remotely, Surfshark helps protect your privacy across all your devices. Included Features Secure encrypted VPN connection Unlimited device support Built-in Ad Blocker Cookie Pop-up Blocker Bypasser (Split Tunneling) Rotating IP Dynamic MultiHop Masked email generator Personal detail generator Key Features 30-day subscription Protect unlimited devices with one subscription Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, iOS, and other supported platforms Encrypted browsing and enhanced online privacy Ideal for streaming, remote work, gaming, and public Wi-Fi Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Surfshark Starter VPN License Type: Subscription Validity: 30 Days Devices: Unlimited Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, iOS, Linux, Smart TVs, and supported browsers Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Surfshark activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your subscription within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional technical support Please note: This license is valid for unlimited devices and includes a 30-day subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>32.95</Price>
    <Code>VPN-SURF30</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/surfshark-starter-vpn-unlimited-devices-2-years-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Network Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/73_20260705_171300_0043.png?v=1783282882</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Secureline VPN | 1 Device | 2 Years</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>Avast SecureLine VPN (1 Device, 2 Years) – Instant Digital Delivery Browse the internet with confidence using Avast SecureLine VPN . Protect your online privacy with military-grade encryption, hide your IP address, and enjoy secure, unrestricted internet access wherever you are. This license includes a 2-year subscription for 1 device . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your VPN and enjoy private browsing right away. What's Included Avast SecureLine VPN activation key Valid for 1 device 2-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Avast SecureLine VPN? Avast SecureLine VPN encrypts your internet connection to help protect your personal data from hackers, internet service providers, advertisers, and other third parties. Whether you're using public Wi-Fi, streaming content, or browsing from home, your online activity remains private and secure. Included Features Encrypted VPN connection for secure browsing Hide your IP address and online activity Protection on public Wi-Fi networks Access to global VPN server locations Fast and stable VPN performance Access geo-restricted content where available Key Features 2-year subscription Protect 1 device Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Private, encrypted internet connection Ideal for browsing, streaming, remote work, and online banking Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Avast SecureLine VPN License Type: Subscription Validity: 2 Years Devices: 1 Device Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Avast SecureLine VPN activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your VPN within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 device and includes a 2-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>31.95</Price>
    <Code>VPN-AVAST2Y1D</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/surfshark-starter-vpn-unlimited-devices-30-days-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Network Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/74_20260705_171300_0044.png?v=1783282841</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Secureline VPN | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>Avast SecureLine VPN (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Browse the internet with confidence using Avast SecureLine VPN . Protect your online privacy with military-grade encryption, hide your IP address, and enjoy secure, unrestricted internet access wherever you are. This license includes a 1-year subscription for 5 devices . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your VPN and enjoy private browsing right away. What's Included Avast SecureLine VPN activation key Valid for 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Avast SecureLine VPN? Avast SecureLine VPN encrypts your internet connection to help protect your personal data from hackers, internet service providers, advertisers, and other third parties. Whether you're using public Wi-Fi, streaming content, or browsing from home, your online activity remains private and secure. Included Features Encrypted VPN connection for secure browsing Hide your IP address and online activity Protection on public Wi-Fi networks Access to global VPN server locations Fast and stable VPN performance Access geo-restricted content where available Key Features 1-year subscription Protect 5 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Private, encrypted internet connection Ideal for browsing, streaming, remote work, and online banking Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Avast SecureLine VPN License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Avast SecureLine VPN activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your VPN within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>48.95</Price>
    <Code>VPN-AVAST1Y5D</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-secureline-vpn-1-device-2-years-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Network Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/75_20260705_171301_0045.png?v=1783282815</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Avast Secureline VPN | 1 Device | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Avast</Brand>
    <Description>Avast SecureLine VPN (1 Device, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Browse the internet with confidence using Avast SecureLine VPN . Protect your online privacy with military-grade encryption, hide your IP address, and enjoy secure, unrestricted internet access wherever you are. This license includes a 1-year subscription for 1 device . With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your VPN and enjoy private browsing right away. What's Included Avast SecureLine VPN activation key Valid for 1 device 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Avast SecureLine VPN? Avast SecureLine VPN encrypts your internet connection to help protect your personal data from hackers, internet service providers, advertisers, and other third parties. Whether you're using public Wi-Fi, streaming content, or browsing from home, your online activity remains private and secure. Included Features Encrypted VPN connection for secure browsing Hide your IP address and online activity Protection on public Wi-Fi networks Access to global VPN server locations Fast and stable VPN performance Access geo-restricted content where available Key Features 1-year subscription Protect 1 device Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Private, encrypted internet connection Ideal for browsing, streaming, remote work, and online banking Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Avast SecureLine VPN License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: 1 Device Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Avast SecureLine VPN activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your VPN within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for 1 device and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your device before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>8.95</Price>
    <Code>VPN-AVAST1Y1D</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-secureline-vpn-5-devices-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Network Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/76_20260705_171301_0046.png?v=1783282776</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2026 | 5 PC | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2026 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your online privacy with Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2026 . Encrypt your internet connection, keep your personal information safe, and browse the web freely with a 1-year subscription for up to 5 devices . Whether you're using public Wi-Fi, working remotely, streaming, or shopping online, Kaspersky VPN helps keep your data private. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your VPN and enjoy secure browsing right away. What's Included Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2026 activation key Valid for up to 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection? Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection creates a secure encrypted tunnel between your device and the internet, helping protect your personal information from hackers, trackers, and unsecured Wi-Fi networks. Browse with confidence while keeping your online activity private. Included Features Encrypted VPN connection for secure browsing Zero-log privacy policy Access to VPN servers around the world High-speed connection with unlimited bandwidth Protection for public Wi-Fi networks Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Private, encrypted internet connection Ideal for browsing, streaming, online banking, gaming, and remote work Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2026 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky VPN activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your VPN within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>10.95</Price>
    <Code>VPN-KSP26</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/avast-secureline-vpn-1-device-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Network Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/77_20260705_171301_0047.png?v=1783281710</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2025 | 5 PC | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Kaspersky</Brand>
    <Description>Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2025 (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Protect your online privacy with Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2025 . Encrypt your internet connection, keep your personal information safe, and browse the web freely with a 1-year subscription for up to 5 devices . Whether you're using public Wi-Fi, working remotely, streaming, or shopping online, Kaspersky VPN helps keep your data private. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your VPN and enjoy secure browsing right away. What's Included Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2025 activation key Valid for up to 5 devices 1-year subscription Activation and installation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection? Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection creates a secure encrypted tunnel between your device and the internet, helping protect your personal information from hackers, trackers, and unsecured Wi-Fi networks. Browse with confidence while keeping your online activity private. Included Features Encrypted VPN connection for secure browsing Zero-log privacy policy Access to VPN servers around the world High-speed connection with unlimited bandwidth Protection for public Wi-Fi networks Key Features 1-year subscription Protect up to 5 devices Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Private, encrypted internet connection Ideal for browsing, streaming, online banking, gaming, and remote work Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Kaspersky VPN Secure Connection 2025 License Type: Subscription Validity: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 Devices Supported Platforms: Windows, macOS, Android, and iOS Activation: Online using your activation key Instant Digital Delivery Your Kaspersky VPN activation key will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your VPN within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation key Activation and installation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This license is valid for up to 5 devices and includes a 1-year subscription . Please verify compatibility with your devices before purchasing to ensure you select the correct product for your needs.</Description>
    <Price>25.95</Price>
    <Code>VPN-KSP25</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/kaspersky-vpn-secure-connection-2026-5-pc-1-year-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Network Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/78_20260705_171301_0048.png?v=1783281674</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Xbox Game Pass Essential - 1 Month</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Xbox Game Pass Essential (1 Month) – Instant Digital Delivery Enjoy online multiplayer and access a growing collection of great games with Xbox Game Pass Essential . Play on Xbox consoles, Windows PC, and supported devices while taking advantage of exclusive member discounts, cloud streaming features, and in-game rewards with a 1-month subscription . With SAIVERA , your subscription code is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your membership and start playing right away. What's Included Xbox Game Pass Essential subscription code 1-month subscription Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Xbox Game Pass Essential? Xbox Game Pass Essential gives you access to online console multiplayer and a library of quality games while offering exclusive member discounts and additional gaming benefits. Download or stream supported titles and enjoy a better gaming experience across your Xbox devices. Included Features Access to over 50 games Online multiplayer for Xbox consoles Game streaming for supported titles and eligible owned games Exclusive member discounts on games and add-ons In-game benefits for selected titles such as League of Legends and Call of Duty: Warzone Microsoft Rewards opportunities through eligible purchases and gameplay Key Features 1-month subscription Play on Xbox consoles, Windows PC, and supported devices Download or stream supported games Regularly updated game library Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Xbox Game Pass Essential License Type: Digital Subscription Validity: 1 Month Activation: Redeem your code with your Microsoft account Supported Platforms: Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One, Windows PC, and supported devices Instant Digital Delivery Your Xbox Game Pass Essential code will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased code anytime from your SAIVERA account and redeem it within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine subscription code Activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Available games, streaming features, member benefits, and online services may vary by country or region and are subject to Microsoft's terms and service updates.</Description>
    <Price>12.95</Price>
    <Code>XBOX-GPE1</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/xbox-game-pass-essential-1-month</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Product Add-Ons &gt; Subscription Services</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/23_20260705_194347_0022.png?v=1783281547</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Xbox Game Pass Essential - 3 Months</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Xbox Game Pass Essential (3 Months) – Instant Digital Delivery Enjoy online multiplayer and access a growing collection of great games with Xbox Game Pass Essential . Play on Xbox consoles, Windows PC, and supported devices while taking advantage of exclusive member discounts, cloud streaming features, and in-game rewards with a 3-month subscription . With SAIVERA , your subscription code is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your membership and start playing right away. What's Included Xbox Game Pass Essential subscription code 3-month subscription Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Xbox Game Pass Essential? Xbox Game Pass Essential gives you access to online console multiplayer and a library of quality games while offering exclusive member discounts and additional gaming benefits. Download or stream supported titles and enjoy a better gaming experience across your Xbox devices. Included Features Access to over 50 games Online multiplayer for Xbox consoles Game streaming for supported titles and eligible owned games Exclusive member discounts on games and add-ons In-game benefits for selected titles such as League of Legends and Call of Duty: Warzone Microsoft Rewards opportunities through eligible purchases and gameplay Key Features 3-month subscription Play on Xbox consoles, Windows PC, and supported devices Download or stream supported games Regularly updated game library Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Xbox Game Pass Essential License Type: Digital Subscription Validity: 3 Months Activation: Redeem your code with your Microsoft account Supported Platforms: Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One, Windows PC, and supported devices Instant Digital Delivery Your Xbox Game Pass Essential code will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased code anytime from your SAIVERA account and redeem it within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine subscription code Activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Available games, streaming features, member benefits, and online services may vary by country or region and are subject to Microsoft's terms and service updates.</Description>
    <Price>31.95</Price>
    <Code>XBOX-GPE3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/xbox-game-pass-essential-3-month</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Product Add-Ons &gt; Subscription Services</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/24_20260705_194347_0023.png?v=1783281531</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Xbox Game Pass Ultimate - 1 Month</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Xbox Game Pass Ultimate (1 Month) – Instant Digital Delivery Unlock the ultimate gaming experience with Xbox Game Pass Ultimate . Enjoy unlimited access to hundreds of high-quality games across Xbox consoles, PC, and supported cloud devices. Play brand-new releases on day one, stream games without downloads, and take advantage of exclusive member benefits with a 1-month subscription . With SAIVERA , your subscription code is delivered digitally within minutes, so you can start playing your favorite games right away. What's Included Xbox Game Pass Ultimate subscription code 1-month subscription Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Xbox Game Pass Ultimate? Xbox Game Pass Ultimate gives you access to an ever-growing library of hundreds of games, including blockbuster releases available on launch day. Play across Xbox consoles, Windows PCs, and supported cloud gaming devices with a single subscription. Included Features Access to over 400 high-quality games New games available on day one Cloud Gaming on supported devices Online console multiplayer EA Play membership included Ubisoft+ Classics included Fortnite Crew benefits included (where applicable) Exclusive in-game benefits for selected titles such as League of Legends and Call of Duty: Warzone High-quality game streaming with priority access Key Features 1-month subscription Play on Xbox consoles, Windows PC, and supported mobile devices Download or stream supported games Access a constantly updated game library Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Xbox Game Pass Ultimate License Type: Digital Subscription Validity: 1 Month Activation: Redeem your code with your Microsoft account Supported Platforms: Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One, Windows PC, Cloud Gaming on supported devices Instant Digital Delivery Your Xbox Game Pass Ultimate code will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased code anytime from your SAIVERA account and redeem it within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine subscription code Activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Subscription availability, included games, cloud gaming, and member benefits may vary by country or region and are subject to Microsoft's terms and service updates.</Description>
    <Price>22.95</Price>
    <Code>XBOX-GPU1</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/xbox-game-pass-ultimate-1-month</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Product Add-Ons &gt; Subscription Services</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/25_20260705_194347_0024_81fc1570-9226-42d3-b59f-ea5612acbef7.png?v=1783281574</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Xbox Game Pass Ultimate - 3 Months</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Xbox Game Pass Ultimate (3 Months) – Instant Digital Delivery Unlock the ultimate gaming experience with Xbox Game Pass Ultimate . Enjoy unlimited access to hundreds of high-quality games across Xbox consoles, PC, and supported cloud devices. Play brand-new releases on day one, stream games without downloads, and take advantage of exclusive member benefits with a 3-month subscription . With SAIVERA , your subscription code is delivered digitally within minutes, so you can start playing your favorite games right away. What's Included Xbox Game Pass Ultimate subscription code 3-month subscription Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Xbox Game Pass Ultimate? Xbox Game Pass Ultimate gives you access to an ever-growing library of hundreds of games, including blockbuster releases available on launch day. Play across Xbox consoles, Windows PCs, and supported cloud gaming devices with a single subscription. Included Features Access to over 400 high-quality games New games available on day one Cloud Gaming on supported devices Online console multiplayer EA Play membership included Ubisoft+ Classics included Fortnite Crew benefits included (where applicable) Exclusive in-game benefits for selected titles such as League of Legends and Call of Duty: Warzone High-quality game streaming with priority access Key Features 3-month subscription Play on Xbox consoles, Windows PC, and supported mobile devices Download or stream supported games Access a constantly updated game library Fast digital delivery License Information Product: Xbox Game Pass Ultimate License Type: Digital Subscription Validity: 3 Months Activation: Redeem your code with your Microsoft account Supported Platforms: Xbox Series X|S, Xbox One, Windows PC, Cloud Gaming on supported devices Instant Digital Delivery Your Xbox Game Pass Ultimate code will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased code anytime from your SAIVERA account and redeem it within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine subscription code Activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Subscription availability, included games, cloud gaming, and member benefits may vary by country or region and are subject to Microsoft's terms and service updates.</Description>
    <Price>60.95</Price>
    <Code>XBOX-GPU3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/xbox-game-pass-ultimate-3-month</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Product Add-Ons &gt; Subscription Services</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/26_20260705_194347_0025.png?v=1783281396</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Youtube Premium - 1 Month</Name>
    <Brand>Google</Brand>
    <Description>YouTube Premium (1 Month) – Instant Digital Delivery Enjoy an uninterrupted entertainment experience with YouTube Premium . Watch videos without ads, download content for offline viewing, and listen to millions of songs with YouTube Music Premium . This package includes a 1-month YouTube Premium account delivered digitally. With SAIVERA , your account details are delivered within minutes, so you can start enjoying premium YouTube features right away. What's Included YouTube Premium account 1-month subscription Activation and login instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose YouTube Premium? YouTube Premium lets you enjoy videos and music without interruptions. Watch ad-free, download content for offline viewing, and continue playing videos or music while using other apps or with your screen locked. Your subscription also includes YouTube Music Premium . Included Features Ad-free video streaming Offline video downloads Background playback YouTube Music Premium included Ad-free music streaming Offline music downloads Key Features 1-month subscription Delivered as a YouTube Premium account Watch videos without advertisements Listen to music with YouTube Music Premium Compatible with smartphones, tablets, computers, and supported smart TVs Fast digital delivery Account Information Product: YouTube Premium Delivery Type: Preconfigured Premium Account Validity: 1 Month Included Services: YouTube Premium &amp; YouTube Music Premium Delivery Method: Account credentials sent by email Instant Digital Delivery Your YouTube Premium account details will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your account information anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed working Premium account Login and activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is delivered as a preconfigured YouTube Premium account , not as a redeemable activation code. Please read the included instructions before using the account.</Description>
    <Price>9.95</Price>
    <Code>YT-PRE1</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/youtube-premium-1-month</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/27_20260705_194347_0026.png?v=1783281325</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Youtube Premium - 3 Months</Name>
    <Brand>Google</Brand>
    <Description>YouTube Premium (3 Months) – Instant Digital Delivery Enjoy your favorite videos and music without interruptions with YouTube Premium . Watch ad-free videos, download content for offline viewing, and listen to music with YouTube Music Premium . Keep videos and music playing in the background while using other apps with a 3-month subscription . With SAIVERA , your activation code is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your subscription and start enjoying premium features right away. What's Included YouTube Premium activation code 3-month subscription Activation instructions Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose YouTube Premium? YouTube Premium enhances your entertainment experience by removing ads, enabling background playback, and allowing offline downloads. Your subscription also includes access to YouTube Music Premium , giving you millions of songs without ads. Included Features Ad-free video streaming Offline video downloads Background playback YouTube Music Premium included Ad-free music streaming Offline music downloads Key Features 3-month subscription Watch videos without advertisements Listen to music with YouTube Music Premium Continue playback while using other apps or with the screen locked Compatible with smartphones, tablets, computers, and supported smart TVs Fast digital delivery License Information Product: YouTube Premium License Type: Digital Subscription Validity: 3 Months Activation: Redeem using your activation code Included Services: YouTube Premium &amp; YouTube Music Premium Instant Digital Delivery Your YouTube Premium activation code will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased code anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your subscription within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support Guaranteed genuine activation code Activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Subscription availability and eligibility may vary by country or region. Please verify that your Google account is eligible for redemption before purchasing.</Description>
    <Price>28.95</Price>
    <Code>YT-PRE3</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/youtube-premium-3-months</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/28_20260705_194347_0027.png?v=1783281307</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Youtube Premium - 12 Months</Name>
    <Brand>Google</Brand>
    <Description>YouTube Premium Subscription (12 Months) – Global Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Enjoy a full year of YouTube Premium with our secure Global Activation service. Watch videos without ads, enjoy background playback, download content for offline viewing, and access YouTube Music Premium . Your subscription is activated through an official Google invitation link , with no need to share your password or login credentials. With SAIVERA , you'll receive your activation link shortly after purchase, allowing you to activate your 12-month subscription within minutes. What's Included 12-month YouTube Premium subscription Official Google activation link Activation instructions Instant digital delivery Friendly customer support How Activation Works Complete your purchase. Receive the official Google activation link. Open the link while signed in to your Google account. Accept the invitation and enjoy YouTube Premium instantly. Why Choose YouTube Premium? Enjoy an uninterrupted entertainment experience with ad-free videos, offline downloads, background playback, and full access to YouTube Music Premium . Stream your favorite content on smartphones, tablets, computers, and supported smart TVs. Included Features 12-month YouTube Premium subscription Ad-free video streaming Background playback Offline video downloads YouTube Music Premium included Official Google activation No VPN required No password sharing required License Information Product: YouTube Premium License Type: Digital Subscription Validity: 12 Months Activation Method: Official Google invitation link Delivery: Instant digital delivery Important Information The activation link is valid for 2 hours after delivery. Please remain available for approximately 20–30 minutes after purchase if activation assistance is required. Your Google account must not already have an active YouTube Premium subscription . No refunds or cancellations are available after the activation link has been delivered. Safety &amp; Transparency Official Google activation method No email password or login credentials required Secure activation process Works globally in supported regions Delivery guarantee at the time of activation Please note: We guarantee successful activation when the service is delivered. If Google changes its activation policies or Terms of Service in the future, refunds or replacements may not be possible unless supported by our provider. Instant Digital Delivery Your activation link will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your activation details anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support Fast activation assistance Friendly and professional customer support Reliable digital delivery</Description>
    <Price>79.95</Price>
    <Code>YT-PRE12</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/youtube-premium-12-months</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/29_20260705_194347_0028.png?v=1783279134</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Office 365 Account | 5 Devices | 1 Year</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Microsoft Office 365 A3 Account (5 Devices, 1 Year) – Instant Digital Delivery Enjoy premium Microsoft Office applications with a Microsoft Office 365 A3 account valid for 1 year . Install and use Office on up to 5 devices , including Windows PCs, Macs, Android devices, iPhones, and tablets. Perfect for work, study, and everyday productivity with access to always up-to-date Office applications. With SAIVERA , your account credentials are delivered digitally within minutes, so you can sign in and start using Office immediately. What's Included Microsoft Office 365 A3 account Pre-generated username and temporary password Valid for up to 5 devices 1-year subscription Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Office 365 A3? Office 365 A3 gives you access to Microsoft's premium productivity tools across multiple devices. Whether you're working, studying, collaborating, or creating documents, you can enjoy the latest Office applications with the flexibility of using them on several devices under one account. Included Applications Microsoft Word Microsoft Excel Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Outlook Microsoft OneNote Microsoft Teams (availability may vary) Key Features 1-year Office 365 subscription Use on up to 5 devices simultaneously Compatible with Windows, macOS, Android, iPhone, and tablets Password can be changed after your first login Access to always up-to-date Office applications Fast digital delivery Account Information Product: Microsoft Office 365 A3 Account Type: Pre-generated Microsoft account Subscription: 1 Year Devices: Up to 5 devices Supported Platforms: Windows PC, Mac, Android, iPhone, and Tablets Username: Pre-generated and cannot be changed Password: Can be changed after your first login Important Information OneDrive storage is not included or guaranteed . If OneDrive is available, we do not recommend storing important files , as Microsoft may restrict or disable access at any time. This product is supplied as a pre-generated Microsoft account. Instant Digital Delivery Your Office 365 account credentials will be delivered shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased account anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 30-day one-to-one replacement warranty for account access issues Guaranteed authentic Microsoft account Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product is a pre-generated Microsoft Office 365 A3 account . The account username cannot be changed, while the password can be updated after your first login. Please ensure you are purchasing the correct product before completing your order, as delivered digital products cannot be exchanged or refunded for incorrect purchases.</Description>
    <Price>4.99</Price>
    <Code>OFF-365Y1</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/office-365-account-5-devices-1-year</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Office Application Software</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/19_20260621_133302_0018.png?v=1783336446</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>007: First Light | PC | Steam Account</Name>
    <Brand>IO Interactive</Brand>
    <Description>Immerse yourself in the story of James Bond’s origins—a young, resourceful, and sometimes reckless trainee agent in the MI6 training program—and discover how he became the world’s most famous spy. After a heroic act, young naval pilot James Bond is offered a chance to join the newly reactivated Double-0 program. However, when a mission to stop a rogue agent ends in tragedy, he must join forces with his reluctant mentor, Greenway, to expose a deep-seated conspiracy and stop an impending coup at the heart of the state. Become 007 and discover a new, standalone, reimagined origin story of James Bond and the events that lead a daring young hero to become MI6’s top agent. Enjoy a thrilling spy adventure featuring missions in breathtaking locations, driving iconic vehicles, and a cinematic quest to track down a rogue agent who’s always one step ahead. Choose your approach: stealthy or loud. Fight with your fists or with fire, use gadgets to infiltrate, or bluff your way past the guards. The choice is entirely yours. Welcome to MI6! Put yourself to the test and replay your favorite missions with additional challenges for endless spy-themed fun. Digital delivery: The product will be delivered via email.</Description>
    <Price>39.99</Price>
    <Code>GAME-007</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/007-first-light-steam-account-for-pc</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Video Game Software &gt; Digital Video Games</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/102.webp?v=1783548516</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Arc Raiders | PC | Steam Account | Global</Name>
    <Brand>Embark Studios</Brand>
    <Description>Arc Raiders – Revolutionary Game of &amp; nbsp; extraction &amp; nbsp; multiplayer on SAIVera Prepare for the decisive multiplayer adventure with Arc Raiders, innovative Shooter &amp; nbsp; of &amp; nbsp; extraction which catapults players into a future land devastated and dominated by lethal mechanized threats. This intense game of survival offers a screaming PvPve gameplay in which the strategic team coordination of a subdivided increasingly important subdivided team it becomes essential to survive both human opponents and mysterious Arc forces. SAIVera is proud to present this highly anticipated Dation game which combines Tactical combat with mechanics of extraction high risk, creating an experience of game unprecedented that will test your skills, your strategy and your survival instinct in the world Post-apocalyptic most hostile ever conceived. Master the Tactical survival in a Futuristic battlefield it crosses insidious environments where every decision determines life or death in this revolutionary Competitive shooter which redefines the Multiplayer game . Arc Raiders Challenge players to outwit both the controlled Mechanized Enemies and the rival teams while securing valuable resources in dangerous mining missions . This Cooperative shooter requires a Strategic planning Perfect and impeccable execution as you face limplacable threat arc through Battle scenarios dynamic. live Arc Raiders means Digital MS Deals and join the struggle for the survival of humanity in the most exciting Extraction Adventure which combines Intense action , Tactical depth and Multiplayer emotion in a Game masterpiece unforgettable.</Description>
    <Price>30.99</Price>
    <Code>GAME-ARCRAIDERS</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/007-first-light-steam-account-for-pc-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Video Game Software &gt; Digital Video Games</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/103.webp?v=1783548958</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Crimson Desert | PC | Steam Account</Name>
    <Brand>Pearl Abyss</Brand>
    <Description>Crimson Desert – Account Steam PC Crimson Desert is an open-world action-adventure game set on the continent of Pywel. Explore uncharted lands, encounter mysterious factions, and experience this formidable world firsthand. The game follows the adventures of Kliff, the Greymane, as he seeks to reclaim all that was lost following a brutal attack by the Black Bears. Key Details License type: Steam PC account Delivery method: Digital delivery via email Installation instructions: Available after purchase What You Get Steam PC Account Information Digital delivery via email Activation and Installation Instructions Game Features A seamless open world Various destinations and storylines Brutal combat and nonstop action</Description>
    <Price>50.99</Price>
    <Code>GAME-CD</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/arc-raiders-pc-steam-account-global-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Video Game Software &gt; Digital Video Games</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/104.webp?v=1783549600</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>EA SPORTS FC 26 | PC | Steam Account</Name>
    <Brand>Electronic Arts</Brand>
    <Description>EA SPORTS FC 26 PC Steam Account EA SPORTS FC 26 offers a revamped and improved gaming experience, based on feedback from the community. Enjoy a more authentic and competitive gaming experience, with new features and game modes. Key details License type: Steam account Delivery method: Digital delivery via email Support available: yes What you'll receive Steam Account Information Digital delivery via email Activation and Installation Instructions Included apps or features EA SPORTS FC 26 Football Ultimate Team Career Mode Clubs</Description>
    <Price>4.99</Price>
    <Code>GAME-FC26</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/crimson-desert-account-steam-pc-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Video Game Software &gt; Digital Video Games</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/105.webp?v=1783550259</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Minecraft Java and Bedrock Edition | PC | Windows Account | Global</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Let your creativity run wild as you enjoy the best of both worlds with Minecraft: Java &amp; Bedrock Editions! Create, survive, battle, or even destroy—these are your only goals as you dive into the fascinating world of Minecraft! Double your mining and crafting with Minecraft: Java &amp; Bedrock Editions! Key Features The best of both worlds: Enjoy a seamless and exciting gaming experience while playing both editions of Minecraft. Now, with a unified launcher, you can easily switch between the two editions! Cross-play with any other Minecraft edition is now easier than ever, as you can easily switch between editions with your friends! The world is your canvas: If you can dream it, you can build it in Creative Mode. It lets you create the gameplay of your dreams! Whether you want to build miniature houses or majestic castles, the choice is yours! Don’t worry about your resources—you have access to unlimited resources in Creative Mode! There’s something for everyone; all you have to do is let your imagination run wild! Survive and thrive in Survival Mode: Fight hordes of mobs, build a shelter, or even travel across different terrains—because your only goal is survival! For all those craving adventure, Minecraft has you covered! Craft your own weapons and gear as you trek through dangerous mountains, battle the worst mobs, or form alliances with other Minecraft players to complete quests; the choice is yours! New tools, locations, and adventures: Explore new tools and locations as you venture through the Bedrock and Java editions. To ensure you have the best gaming experience possible, keep your game up to date and complete quests to get the most out of this world of mining and crafting! Enjoy a seamless gaming experience with Minecraft: Java &amp; Bedrock Editions, featuring an immersive multiplayer experience (for up to 8 players) as you explore new and exciting realms you’ve never seen before!</Description>
    <Price>18.99</Price>
    <Code>GAME-MC</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/ea-sports-fc-26-pc-steam-account-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Video Game Software &gt; Digital Video Games</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/106.webp?v=1783550542</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Nioh 3 | PC | Steam Account</Name>
    <Brand>Koei Tecmo</Brand>
    <Description>Nioh 3 PC Account Steam Nioh 3 is the latest game in the dark samurai action RPG series. This title offers an open-world environment that will push you to your limits, allowing you to explore freely. Immerse yourself in a world of dark samurai, face formidable yokai, explore eerie villages, and battle the menacing presence of &quot;The Crucible.&quot; Key Details Product type: Steam account Delivery method: Digital delivery via email Support: No support included What You Get Steam account credentials Digital delivery via email Fighting Styles Samurai Style: Intense, head-on combat Ninja Style: Quick Moves and Special Techniques</Description>
    <Price>45.99</Price>
    <Code>GAME-NIOH</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/minecraft-java-and-bedrock-edition-global-pc-windows-account-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Video Game Software &gt; Digital Video Games</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/107.webp?v=1783550792</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Resident Evil Requiem | PC | Steam CD Key</Name>
    <Brand>Capcom</Brand>
    <Description>Resident Evil Requiem PC Steam CD Key Immerse yourself in a survival horror experience with Resident Evil Requiem, available for PC via Steam. This game offers a gripping story with richly developed characters and gameplay that’s more immersive than ever. Return to Raccoon City, a city of disaster and despair, and face your nightmares. Key Details Title: Resident Evil Requiem Platform: PC Distribution: Steam License type: Digital CD key What You Get Digital CD key for activation on Steam Digital delivery via email Activation and Installation Instructions Game Features A classic survival horror experience featuring combat, investigation, puzzles, and resource management You can switch between first-person and third-person view to face the horrors in a way that suits your playstyle</Description>
    <Price>57.99</Price>
    <Code>GAME-RER</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/nioh-3-pc-account-steam-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Video Game Software &gt; Digital Video Games</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/108.webp?v=1783550833</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Pro | Retail | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Pro Retail License Key (1 PC) – Instant Digital Delivery Upgrade your PC with a genuine Windows 11 Pro Retail license and unlock powerful features designed for work, study, gaming, and everyday use. Enjoy enhanced security, smooth performance, and a modern Windows experience with a lifetime activation for one PC. With SAIVERA , your license is delivered digitally, so you can activate your system and get started within minutes. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Pro Retail license key Valid for activation on 1 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery Customer support if you need assistance Why Choose Windows 11 Pro? Whether you're upgrading an existing PC or installing Windows on a new one, the Pro edition offers advanced features beyond the Home version, making it ideal for professionals, students, businesses, and power users. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Lifetime activation for one PC Reactivate Windows after reinstalling on the same device Advanced security with BitLocker Remote Desktop support Hyper-V virtualization Fast, stable, and secure performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 11 Pro Activation: Online Devices: 1 PC Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same PC Transfer to another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, and your purchased license can be accessed anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Genuine and authentic license Friendly customer support whenever you need help Please note: Make sure you purchase the correct Windows edition for your device before completing your order. If you're unsure which version you need, our support team will be happy to assist you before your purchase.</Description>
    <Price>3.30</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11PRO</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-11-pro-retail-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091255_0001.png?v=1784409326</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Pro | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Pro Retail License Key (5 PC) – Instant Digital Delivery Upgrade your PC with a genuine Windows 11 Pro Retail license and unlock powerful features designed for work, study, gaming, and everyday use. Enjoy enhanced security, smooth performance, and a modern Windows experience with a lifetime activation for one PC. With SAIVERA , your license is delivered digitally, so you can activate your system and get started within minutes. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Pro Retail license key Valid for activation on 5 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery Customer support if you need assistance Why Choose Windows 11 Pro? Whether you're upgrading an existing PC or installing Windows on a new one, the Pro edition offers advanced features beyond the Home version, making it ideal for professionals, students, businesses, and power users. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Lifetime activation for one PC Reactivate Windows after reinstalling on the same device Advanced security with BitLocker Remote Desktop support Hyper-V virtualization Fast, stable, and secure performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 11 Pro Activation: Online Devices: 5 PC Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same PC Transfer to another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, and your purchased license can be accessed anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Genuine and authentic license Friendly customer support whenever you need help Please note: Make sure you purchase the correct Windows edition for your device before completing your order. If you're unsure which version you need, our support team will be happy to assist you before your purchase.</Description>
    <Price>36.95</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11PRO5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-11-pro-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0003.png?v=1784409536</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Home | OEM | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Home OEM License Key (1 PC) – Instant Digital Delivery Upgrade your PC with a genuine Windows 11 Home OEM license and enjoy a smooth, secure, and reliable Windows experience. Perfect for everyday computing, home use, work, and study, this lifetime license provides genuine Microsoft activation for one device. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate Windows quickly and start using your PC without delay. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Home OEM license key Valid for activation on 1 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Home? Windows Home delivers everything you need for everyday computing, including fast performance, built-in security, and compatibility with the latest applications. Whether you're browsing the web, studying, streaming, or working from home, Windows Home offers a smooth and familiar experience. Key Features Genuine Microsoft OEM license Lifetime activation for one PC Online activation Automatically reactivates after reinstalling Windows on the same device Fast, secure, and reliable performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates Ideal for home, study, and everyday use License Information License Type: OEM Supported Edition: Windows 11 Home Activation: Online Devices: 1 PC Validity: Lifetime activation Motherboard Binding: The license becomes permanently linked to the activated motherboard. Reinstallation: Supported on the same device with automatic reactivation. Transfer to Another PC: Not supported. OEM licenses cannot be moved to a different device after activation. Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, and your purchased license can be accessed anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, make sure you select the correct Windows edition for your PC. OEM licenses are designed for a single device and become permanently associated with the motherboard after activation.</Description>
    <Price>5.20</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11HOME</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-home-oem-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0007_37f927c3-62cd-4256-a345-fd3f05777106.png?v=1784411573</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Pro | Retail | 50 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Pro Retail License Key (50 PCs) – Instant Digital Delivery Activate up to 50 PCs with a genuine Windows 11 Pro Retail license. Ideal for businesses, IT professionals, schools, and organizations managing multiple devices, this Retail license provides lifetime activation, online activation, and the flexibility to reinstall Windows on the same activated PCs whenever needed. With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate multiple devices quickly and efficiently without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Pro Retail license key Valid for activation on up to 50 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Pro? Windows Pro is built for professionals and organizations that require advanced security, productivity, and management features. From BitLocker encryption and Remote Desktop to Hyper-V virtualization, Windows Pro provides everything needed for modern business and professional environments. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Activate up to 50 PCs Lifetime activation Online activation Reinstall Windows and reactivate on the same activated devices Advanced security with BitLocker encryption Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 11 Pro Activation: Online Devices: Up to 50 PCs Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs Transfer to Another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and begin activating your devices within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 30-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, ensure you select the correct Windows edition for your devices. If you need assistance choosing the right license, our support team will be happy to help before your purchase.</Description>
    <Price>44.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11PRO50</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-11-pro-retail-50-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0005.png?v=1784411834</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Home | Retail | 5 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Home Retail License Key (5 PCs) – Instant Digital Delivery Activate up to 5 PCs with a genuine Windows 11 Home Retail license. Designed for families, businesses, and users with multiple devices, this Retail license provides lifetime activation, online activation, and the flexibility to reinstall Windows on the same activated PCs whenever needed. With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, so you can activate your devices quickly and enjoy a genuine Windows experience without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Home Retail license key Valid for activation on up to 5 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Home? Windows Home is built for everyday computing, offering a fast, secure, and intuitive experience. Whether you're browsing, studying, streaming, working remotely, or managing multiple household computers, Windows Home delivers the reliability and performance you need. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Activate up to 5 PCs Lifetime activation Online activation Reinstall Windows and reactivate on the same activated devices Fast, secure, and reliable performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates Perfect for home users, families, and multiple-device setups License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 11 Home Activation: Online Devices: Up to 5 PCs Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs Transfer to Another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your devices within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, ensure you select the correct Windows edition for your devices. If you're unsure which version is right for you, our support team will be happy to help before you place your order.</Description>
    <Price>27.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11HOME5</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-home-retail-5-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0009.png?v=1784412070</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Pro for Workstation | Retail | 2 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Pro for Workstations Retail License Key (2 PCs) – Lifetime Activation Activate up to 2 PCs with a genuine Windows 11 Pro for Workstations Retail license. Designed for professionals, creators, engineers, developers, and power users, Windows Pro for Workstations delivers advanced performance, security, and reliability for demanding workloads. With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your devices quickly and enjoy a genuine Windows experience without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Pro for Workstations Retail license key Valid for activation on up to 2 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Pro for Workstations? Windows Pro for Workstations is designed for users who need more than standard Windows editions can offer. It provides advanced capabilities for demanding professional applications, intensive data processing, high-performance computing, and other resource-intensive workloads. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Retail license Activate up to 2 PCs Lifetime activation Online activation Reinstall Windows and reactivate on the same activated devices Support for high-performance hardware configurations Advanced security with BitLocker encryption Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Fast, stable, and reliable performance for demanding workloads Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Retail Supported Edition: Windows 11 Pro for Workstations Activation: Online Devices: Up to 2 PCs Validity: Lifetime activation Reinstallation: Supported on the same activated PCs Transfer to Another PC: Supported according to Microsoft's Retail license policy Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your devices within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, ensure you select the correct Windows edition for your devices. Windows Pro for Workstations is designed for high-performance professional use. If you're unsure whether this edition is right for your PC, our support team will be happy to help before you place your order.</Description>
    <Price>14.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11PROWORK</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-pro-for-workstation-retail-2-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0013.png?v=1784412486</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Enterprise | MAK Volume | 50 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume License Key (50 PCs) – Lifetime Activation Activate up to 50 PCs with a genuine Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume license. Designed for businesses, organizations, IT professionals, and professional environments, Windows 11 Enterprise provides advanced security, management, and productivity features for multiple devices. With SAIVERA , your license key is delivered digitally, allowing you to activate your devices quickly and efficiently without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume license key Valid for activation on up to 50 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Enterprise? Windows 11 Enterprise is designed for organizations that require advanced security, centralized management, and enhanced control over their IT environments. It is ideal for businesses and professional users managing multiple PCs and requiring enterprise-level Windows features. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Volume license MAK (Multiple Activation Key) activation Activate up to 50 PCs Lifetime license validity Advanced security and threat protection BitLocker drive encryption Windows Defender and enterprise security features Advanced device and application management Remote Desktop and virtualization support Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: MAK Volume Supported Edition: Windows 11 Enterprise Activation: Online Devices: Up to 50 PCs Validity: Lifetime license Reinstallation: Activation availability may depend on the remaining activations assigned to the MAK key Transfer to Another PC: Subject to Microsoft Volume Licensing activation terms Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your devices efficiently. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This is a Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume license intended for activation on up to 50 PCs. Make sure your devices are compatible with the Enterprise edition and that you select the correct license type before purchasing.</Description>
    <Price>19.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11EN50</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-11-enterprise-mak-volume-50-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0015.png?v=1784412805</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Pro | OEM | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Pro OEM License Key (1 PC) – Instant Digital Delivery Upgrade your PC with a genuine Windows 11 Pro OEM license and unlock powerful features designed for professionals, businesses, and advanced users. Enjoy lifetime activation, enhanced security, and reliable performance with an authentic Microsoft OEM license for one device. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your Windows installation quickly and start working without delay. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Pro OEM license key Valid for activation on 1 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step installation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Pro? Windows Pro is built for users who need more than the standard Home edition. Enjoy advanced security, professional management tools, Remote Desktop, BitLocker encryption, and powerful productivity features for business, work, study, or gaming. Key Features Genuine Microsoft OEM license Lifetime activation for one PC Online activation Automatically reactivates after reinstalling Windows on the same device Advanced security with BitLocker encryption Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Fast, stable, and secure performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: OEM Supported Edition: Windows 11 Pro Activation: Online Devices: 1 PC Validity: Lifetime activation Motherboard Binding: The license becomes permanently linked to the activated motherboard. Reinstallation: Supported on the same device with automatic reactivation. Transfer to Another PC: Not supported. OEM licenses cannot be moved to another device after activation. Important: This OEM license cannot be used to upgrade Windows Home to Windows Pro. It is intended for clean installations or devices already running the Pro edition. Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, and your purchased license can be accessed anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, ensure you select the correct Windows edition for your device. OEM licenses are designed for a single PC and become permanently associated with the motherboard after activation.</Description>
    <Price>5.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11PROOEM</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-11-pro-oem-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091255_0001_c1dd7ed9-b452-48c7-95ec-0a91dbd5fc3f.png?v=1784413112</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Pro | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Pro License Key (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Activate Windows 11 Pro on one PC using the official Microsoft Phone Activation method. This is a genuine activation solution for users who need a reliable Windows Pro license with fast digital delivery and easy activation instructions. With SAIVERA , your activation key and phone activation guide are delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your Windows installation quickly and securely. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Pro activation key Valid for activation on 1 PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Official Microsoft download link Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Pro? Windows Pro offers powerful features for professionals, students, businesses, and advanced users. Enjoy enhanced security, improved productivity, Remote Desktop, BitLocker encryption, and compatibility with the latest Windows updates. Key Features Genuine Microsoft activation key Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate 1 PC Advanced security with BitLocker Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Fast, stable, and secure performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Supported Edition: Windows 11 Pro Devices: 1 PC Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method. It is intended for a single activation on one PC. Reactivation after formatting, hardware changes, or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>3.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11PROPH</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-pro-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091255_0001_efa9c833-40f8-4a36-886b-868d12f7a58a.png?v=1784413437</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Home | Activate by Phone | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Home License Key (1 PC) – Phone Activation – Instant Digital Delivery Activate Windows 11 Home on one PC using the official Microsoft Phone Activation method. This genuine activation solution is perfect for home users looking for a secure, reliable Windows license with fast digital delivery and simple activation. With SAIVERA , your activation key and phone activation instructions are delivered digitally within minutes, so you can activate Windows quickly and start using your PC without delay. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Home activation key Valid for activation on 1 PC Microsoft Phone Activation instructions Official Microsoft download link Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Home? Windows Home delivers everything you need for everyday computing, including a modern interface, reliable security, and smooth performance. It's the ideal choice for browsing, streaming, studying, working from home, and enjoying your favorite apps. Key Features Genuine Microsoft activation key Official Microsoft Phone Activation method Activate 1 PC Fast, stable, and secure Windows experience Compatible with the latest Windows updates Perfect for home, study, and everyday use License Information Activation Method: Microsoft Phone Activation Supported Edition: Windows 11 Home Devices: 1 PC Activation: One-time activation Reinstallation: Reactivation after formatting or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed . Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key and phone activation instructions will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft activation key Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This product uses the Microsoft Phone Activation method. It is intended for a single activation on one PC. Reactivation after formatting, hardware changes, or reinstalling Windows is not guaranteed.</Description>
    <Price>3.49</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11HOMEPH</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-11-home-activate-by-phone-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091256_0007_9d0102d3-53ea-48df-aa16-cd0d4d8eb7be.png?v=1784415235</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Pro | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Pro Volume License Key (20 PCs) – Instant Digital Delivery Activate up to 20 PCs with a genuine Windows 11 Pro Volume License . Designed for businesses, offices, schools, and IT professionals, this volume license offers a convenient way to activate multiple devices while enjoying the advanced features of Windows Pro. With SAIVERA , your volume license key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to deploy Windows quickly across your devices without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Pro Volume license key Valid for activation on up to 20 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Pro? Windows Pro provides advanced tools for productivity, security, and device management, making it the ideal choice for organizations and professionals. Enjoy features such as BitLocker encryption, Remote Desktop, Hyper-V virtualization, and compatibility with the latest Windows updates. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Volume license Activate up to 20 PCs Lifetime activation Ideal for businesses, offices, and educational institutions Advanced security with BitLocker encryption Remote Desktop and Hyper-V support Fast, stable, and secure Windows performance Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: Volume License Supported Edition: Windows 11 Pro Devices: Up to 20 PCs Validity: Lifetime activation Activation: As provided with the supplied volume license key Instant Digital Delivery Your volume license key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased product anytime from your SAIVERA account and begin activating your devices within minutes. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: Before purchasing, verify that you are selecting the correct Windows edition and license type for your environment. If you need assistance, our support team will be happy to help before your purchase.</Description>
    <Price>39.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11PRO20</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-10-pro-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime-copy</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091257_0021.png?v=1784415477</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Enterprise | MAK Volume | 1 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume License Key (1 PC) – Lifetime Activation Activate Windows 11 Enterprise on one PC with a genuine MAK Volume license. Designed for businesses, organizations, IT professionals, and advanced users, Windows 11 Enterprise provides powerful security, management, and productivity features for professional environments. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate your Windows installation quickly and efficiently without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume license key Valid for activation on 1 PC Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Enterprise? Windows 11 Enterprise is designed for organizations and professional users who require advanced security, device management, and enterprise-level features. It provides enhanced protection and control for demanding professional environments. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Volume license MAK (Multiple Activation Key) activation Activate 1 PC Lifetime license validity Advanced security and threat protection BitLocker drive encryption Windows Defender and enterprise security features Advanced device and application management Remote Desktop and virtualization support Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: MAK Volume Supported Edition: Windows 11 Enterprise Activation: Online Devices: 1 PC Validity: Lifetime license Reinstallation: Activation availability may depend on the remaining activations assigned to the MAK key Transfer to Another PC: Subject to Microsoft Volume Licensing activation terms Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your device efficiently. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This is a Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume license intended for activation on 1 PC. Make sure your device is compatible with the Enterprise edition and that you select the correct license type before purchasing.</Description>
    <Price>5.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11EN</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-11-enterprise-mak-volume-1-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091257_0019.png?v=1784415790</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Windows 11 Enterprise | MAK Volume | 20 PC | Lifetime</Name>
    <Brand>Microsoft</Brand>
    <Description>Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume License Key (20 PCs) – Lifetime Activation Activate up to 20 PCs with a genuine Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume license. Designed for businesses, organizations, schools, IT professionals, and advanced users, Windows 11 Enterprise provides powerful security, management, and productivity features for professional environments. With SAIVERA , your activation key is delivered digitally within minutes, allowing you to activate and manage multiple Windows installations efficiently without waiting for physical shipping. What's Included Genuine Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume license key Valid for activation on up to 20 PCs Official Microsoft download link Easy step-by-step activation guide Instant digital delivery by email Friendly customer support Why Choose Windows 11 Enterprise? Windows 11 Enterprise is designed for organizations and professional users who require advanced security, device management, and enterprise-level features. It provides enhanced protection and control for demanding professional environments. Key Features Genuine Microsoft Volume license MAK (Multiple Activation Key) activation Activate up to 20 PCs Lifetime license validity Advanced security and threat protection BitLocker drive encryption Windows Defender and enterprise security features Advanced device and application management Remote Desktop and virtualization support Compatible with the latest Windows updates License Information License Type: MAK Volume Supported Edition: Windows 11 Enterprise Activation: Online Devices: Up to 20 PCs Validity: Lifetime license Reinstallation: Activation availability may depend on the remaining activations assigned to the MAK key Transfer to Another PC: Subject to Microsoft Volume Licensing activation terms Instant Digital Delivery Your activation key will be available shortly after your order is completed. You'll also receive an email notification, allowing you to access your purchased license anytime from your SAIVERA account and activate your devices efficiently. Warranty &amp; Support 7-day replacement warranty for activation issues Guaranteed genuine Microsoft license Friendly and professional customer support Please note: This is a Windows 11 Enterprise MAK Volume license intended for activation on up to 20 PCs. Make sure you select the correct license type for your organization before purchasing.</Description>
    <Price>16.99</Price>
    <Code>WINLIC-11EN20</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/windows-11-enterprise-mak-volume-20-pc-lifetime</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Computer Software &gt; Operating Systems</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/WINDOWS10_11PRO_20260718_091257_0017.png?v=1784415998</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
  <Offer>
    <Name>Rockstar Games Grand Theft Auto VI | PS5 | Account</Name>
    <Brand>Rockstar Games</Brand>
    <Description>Grand Theft Auto VI PS5 Account Experience the next chapter of the legendary Grand Theft Auto series with Grand Theft Auto VI on PlayStation 5. Explore the vibrant state of Leonida, including the neon-soaked streets of Vice City, in Rockstar Games' most ambitious open-world experience yet. Key Details Title: Grand Theft Auto VI Platform: PlayStation 5 Distribution: PlayStation Network License type: Digital Account Important: This product is an account, not a digital game key or CD key What You Get Access to a PlayStation account containing Grand Theft Auto VI Digital delivery via email Activation and Installation Instructions Game Features Explore a vast open-world environment set in the fictional state of Leonida Discover the neon-soaked streets of Vice City and surrounding areas Experience an action-adventure game with an immersive story and open-world gameplay Play as Lucia and her partner as they navigate the criminal underworld of Leonida</Description>
    <Price>71.95</Price>
    <Code>GAME-GTAVI</Code>
    <Link>https://saivera.net/products/rockstar-games-grand-theft-auto-vi-ps5-account</Link>
    <Stock>disponibile</Stock>
    <Categories>Software &gt; Video Game Software &gt; Digital Video Games</Categories>
    <Image>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0599/6632/4816/files/Official_Cover_Art_square.webp?v=1784795767</Image>
    <ShippingCost>0</ShippingCost>
  </Offer>
</Products>
